{"tokens": ["Transcript", "excerpt:", "Host", "Maria:", "We", "are", "joined", "by", "Jamie", "Arnold", "from", "Mcclure,", "Ward", "and", "Lee.", "Jamie", "Arnold:", "I", "lead", "distribution", "manager", "at", "Mcclure,", "Ward", "and", "Lee", "and", "work", "with", "teams", "in", "Traciebury.", "Host", "Maria:", "You", "referenced", "support", "calls", "to", "00420", "718", "370", "1711", "and", "incident", "traffic", "from", "27.24.98.25.", "Jamie", "Arnold:", "Correct,", "and", "some", "audit", "records", "still", "contain", "tokens", "like", "221-98-5515.", "Host", "Maria:", "One", "more", "thing,", "you", "work", "at", "Williams", "and", "Sons", "too,", "right?", "What's", "the", "culture", "like", "there?"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 21, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-IPV4", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["**Episode", "Title:**", "Digital", "Frontlines", "**Guest:**", "Caitlin", "Henderson", "**Company:**", "Bernard", "LLC", "**Transcript", "URL:**", "https://blair.com/episodes/7924", "**Host:**", "Today", "we", "have", "Caitlin", "Henderson,", "who", "works", "at", "Bernard", "LLC.", "Welcome!", "**Caitlin", "Henderson:**", "Thanks", "for", "having", "me.", "My", "work", "at", "Bernard", "LLC", "keeps", "me", "busy.", "**Host:**", "You", "previously", "mentioned", "partnerships", "in", "Melanieview,", "Sri", "Lanka.", "**Caitlin", "Henderson:**", "Yes,", "and", "we", "also", "review", "logs", "like", "155.7.144.51", "and", "identifiers", "such", "as", "224-30-8280.", "**Host:**", "Separate", "question:", "you", "also", "consult", "with", "Davis", "Inc,", "correct?", "What", "is", "it", "like", "working", "there?"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 6, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 21, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["**Episode", "Title:**", "The", "Future", "of", "Media", "**Guest:**", "Allison", "Hill", "**Company:**", "Garcia,", "Yang", "and", "Gardner", "**Transcript", "URL:**", "https://cole.com/episodes/7912", "**Host:**", "Today", "we", "have", "Allison", "Hill,", "who", "works", "at", "Garcia,", "Yang", "and", "Gardner.", "Welcome!", "**Allison", "Hill:**", "Thanks", "for", "having", "me.", "My", "work", "at", "Garcia,", "Yang", "and", "Gardner", "keeps", "me", "busy.", "**Host:**", "You", "previously", "mentioned", "partnerships", "in", "New", "Jamesside,", "Italy.", "**Allison", "Hill:**", "Yes,", "and", "we", "also", "review", "logs", "like", "190.71.63.58", "and", "identifiers", "such", "as", "655-15-0410.", "**Host:**", "Separate", "question:", "you", "also", "consult", "with", "Henderson,", "Johnson", "and", "Robinson,", "correct?", "What", "is", "it", "like", "working", "there?"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 6, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 21, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
