{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "North", "Xavier", "on", "+81", "18", "213", "956", "611.", "Account", "manager", "Heather", "Parrish", "from", "Sparks-Eaton", "will", "respond", "at", "shawdon@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "03/11/2026", "at", "10:44.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://lopez.com/updates/664."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Patricia", "Sanders:", "+61-627-507-9897.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Wyatt", "Ltd;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "adkinssean@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Gary", "Myers", "from", "Robertson", "Group", "was", "held", "in", "North", "Patrick.", "Contact:", "(913)", "431-5914,", "email", "ugraham@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "East", "Gina", "on", "+91", "43", "771", "901", "894.", "Account", "manager", "Allison", "Torres", "from", "Jensen-Branch", "will", "respond", "at", "chanson@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Customer", "Support", "desk", "in", "Welchberg.", "The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Compliance", "Review", "Team.", "Customer", "Support", "Division", "Young", "PLC"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Public", "Services", "on", "the", "customer", "care", "transition.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "James", "Poole", "at", "+995-92-1349-1828", "or", "via", "email", "at", "lloydarthur@example.org.", "James", "Poole", "works", "with", "Curtis,", "Mcdaniel", "and", "Martin", "in", "Joseville."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Samantha", "Thompson", "to", "147858541.", "Current", "employer:", "Jones-Rodriguez."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Public", "Services", "on", "the", "customer", "care", "transition.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Compliance", "Review", "Team.", "Community", "Outreach", "Division", "Barr-Peterson"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "02/09/2026", "at", "12:00.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://hicks.com/updates/791."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Public", "Services", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "German", "citizen", "Paul", "Goodwin", "at", "Hall,", "Vega", "and", "Price.", "SSN:", "501-93-8038,", "callback", "(711)", "763-6530."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Public", "Services", "desk", "in", "Ashleyhaven.", "The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Smithton", "on", "00420", "178", "760", "2479.", "Account", "manager", "Mark", "Powers", "from", "Barton", "Group", "will", "respond", "at", "gbarrett@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Community", "Outreach", "on", "the", "incident", "response", "drill.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Engineering", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Community", "Outreach", "desk", "in", "West", "Kimberlychester.", "The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Carol", "White", "at", "+49-844-474-7606", "or", "via", "email", "at", "umahoney@example.net.", "Carol", "White", "works", "with", "Wagner-Sandoval", "in", "Meganchester."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Government", "Support", "Team.", "Engineering", "Division", "Skinner-James"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Korean", "employee", "Ashley", "Crawford", "at", "Walker,", "Brock", "and", "Simmons", "has", "SSN", "742-11-8205", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(593)", "973-3292."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Laura", "Miller:", "+44", "240", "830", "52", "70.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Weeks", "LLC;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "nichole66@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Public", "Services", "on", "the", "customer", "care", "transition.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Operations", "desk", "in", "Port", "Michelleland.", "The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Brenda", "Lee", "at", "Davies,", "Allen", "and", "Price", "has", "social", "security", "number", "077884594", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Zachary", "Chan", "at", "+61", "844", "534", "20", "65", "or", "via", "email", "at", "aprilmclaughlin@example.org.", "Zachary", "Chan", "works", "with", "Caldwell-Sullivan", "in", "New", "Justinside."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Government", "Support", "Team.", "Customer", "Support", "Division", "Harvey-Allen"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Krista", "Martinez:", "+44-90-658-396-757.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Little-Gonzalez;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "boyerjeff@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Customer", "Support", "Division", "Bryant-Braun"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Kimberly", "Long", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Hayes-White.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "857-51-8117.", "Phone:", "(379)", "627-3880."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook", "on", "03/16/2026", "at", "01:52.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://green-edwards.biz/updates/849."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Engineering", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Engineering", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Andrew", "Gonzales", "at", "+49", "153", "229", "7897", "or", "via", "email", "at", "hernandezheather@example.org.", "Andrew", "Gonzales", "works", "with", "Perez-Adams", "in", "Lake", "Mauriceside."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Customer", "Support", "desk", "in", "Davisbury.", "The", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Operations", "Division", "Mccarty-Taylor"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Engineering", "desk", "in", "Stephensstad.", "The", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Cesar", "Woods:", "+91", "933", "758", "3868.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Kent", "Inc;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "carmen86@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Charles", "Hammond", "at", "lroberts@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Barnes", "LLC", "is", "located", "in", "East", "Adam."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Customer", "Success", "Team.", "Customer", "Support", "Division", "King-Smith"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Mr.", "Steven", "Griffith,", "a", "Japanese", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Riley,", "Barnes", "and", "Burgess", "in", "East", "Joanborough.", "Contact:", "(305)", "226-2468", "or", "jerry15@example.org."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Operations", "desk", "in", "New", "John.", "The", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review", "on", "03/26/2026", "at", "12:25.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://benson-woods.com/updates/554."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Operations", "on", "the", "service", "rollout", "plan.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review", "on", "03/06/2026", "at", "13:36.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://moore.com/updates/567."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "West", "Coreyshire", "on", "00420-153-756-8873.", "Account", "manager", "Brian", "Lambert", "from", "Phelps,", "York", "and", "Randolph", "will", "respond", "at", "enewman@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "James", "Ferguson", "(SSN:", "094-66-7299),", "who", "works", "at", "Duncan", "Group", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(319)", "896-4365", "or", "brookehancock@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "03/05/2026", "at", "10:37.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://lee.com/updates/651."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Operations", "on", "the", "service", "rollout", "plan.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Brian", "Brown", "at", "00420", "217", "880", "5564", "or", "via", "email", "at", "diana43@example.org.", "Brian", "Brown", "works", "with", "Davidson-Hensley", "in", "North", "Linda."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Joseph", "Blankenship:", "+61", "865", "116", "6850.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Barnes,", "Hernandez", "and", "Davis;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "mvalenzuela@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook", "on", "04/04/2026", "at", "18:25.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://byrd.com/updates/950."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Mr.", "Bryan", "Mckinney", "from", "Bryan,", "Lam", "and", "Hayes", "was", "held", "in", "North", "Peterburgh.", "Contact:", "(848)", "510-4965,", "email", "lauren13@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Valdezberg", "on", "+61", "13", "6221", "2623.", "Account", "manager", "Monica", "Mcclain", "from", "Welch,", "Hess", "and", "Riley", "will", "respond", "at", "rebeccaarnold@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review", "on", "03/03/2026", "at", "10:27.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://wright.com/updates/146."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "incident", "response", "drill", "on", "04/03/2026", "at", "11:32.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://wright.com/updates/521."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "03/24/2026", "at", "16:23.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://adams.com/updates/384."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Jonathan", "Parks", "at", "+81", "71", "575", "308", "448", "or", "via", "email", "at", "browndeanna@example.net.", "Jonathan", "Parks", "works", "with", "Galvan-Shea", "in", "East", "Tonymouth."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "03/17/2026", "at", "12:26.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://holland.biz/updates/509."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Kimberly", "Smith:", "+49", "890", "695", "52", "27.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Banks,", "Boyd", "and", "Wood;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "wolferoy@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Barbara", "Johnson,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "088152322,", "employed", "at", "Mack-Gould."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Customer", "Support", "desk", "in", "New", "Sarahview.", "The", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Robert", "Richards", "at", "+49", "48", "564", "174", "805", "or", "via", "email", "at", "perkinshannah@example.net.", "Robert", "Richards", "works", "with", "Mccormick-Smith", "in", "West", "Kelli."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Community", "Outreach", "on", "the", "service", "rollout", "plan.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review", "on", "03/15/2026", "at", "05:02.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://ramos.com/updates/256."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Timothy", "Kennedy:", "+44", "507", "834", "8842.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Johnson", "Group;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "garciachristine@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "03/18/2026", "at", "04:16.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://clements-murphy.com/updates/991."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Julie", "Sims,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "316575897,", "employed", "at", "Hill", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Christine", "Gonzalez,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "657946888,", "employed", "at", "Hill-Flores."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Community", "Outreach", "desk", "in", "Port", "Amandaberg.", "The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Chinese", "employee", "Sara", "Evans", "at", "Williams", "Group", "has", "SSN", "190-18-7823", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(727)", "535-2421."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Derekburgh", "on", "+49", "68", "479", "786", "860.", "Account", "manager", "Sarah", "Valencia", "from", "Brooks", "Ltd", "will", "respond", "at", "vwillis@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Steven", "Friedman:", "+61", "89", "8538", "6928.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Johns-Davis;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "ian66@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Community", "Outreach", "desk", "in", "East", "Aaronmouth.", "The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Greeneshire", "on", "+61", "83", "7825", "4068.", "Account", "manager", "Alison", "Williams", "from", "Vargas,", "Taylor", "and", "Hunt", "will", "respond", "at", "brianscott@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Sharon", "Beard:", "+49", "739", "748", "9984.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Baker-Pena;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "rjohnson@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Kenneth", "Hanson", "from", "Mendez", "Group", "was", "held", "in", "Lake", "Kelly.", "Contact:", "(676)", "514-3616,", "email", "lvasquez@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Community", "Outreach", "desk", "in", "West", "Angela.", "The", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Kim", "Lopez:", "+81", "46", "649", "108", "967.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Sandoval,", "Hudson", "and", "Meza;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "xreese@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Customer", "Support", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Douglas", "Maxwell,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "462800879,", "employed", "at", "Peterson-Bartlett."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Adrian", "Patterson", "at", "patriciavargas@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Wright", "Group", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Tinaton."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Nicholas", "Rush", "at", "+61-806-479-37-66", "or", "via", "email", "at", "whitelucas@example.net.", "Nicholas", "Rush", "works", "with", "Myers,", "Gamble", "and", "Sanford", "in", "Lake", "Ariana."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Community", "Outreach", "Division", "Gomez,", "Duncan", "and", "Lopez"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Customer", "Support", "desk", "in", "Ortizfort.", "The", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Engineering", "desk", "in", "Smithview.", "The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Compliance", "Review", "Team.", "Engineering", "Division", "Pena,", "Marshall", "and", "Ramos"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Engineering", "on", "the", "customer", "care", "transition.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "incident", "response", "drill", "on", "03/27/2026", "at", "04:33.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://richardson.biz/updates/803."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Dr.", "Nicole", "Trujillo", "at", "+61-851-981-6658", "or", "via", "email", "at", "ihoward@example.com.", "Dr.", "Nicole", "Trujillo", "works", "with", "Quinn-Smith", "in", "South", "Jasmineside."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Virginia", "Todd", "at", "Thompson", "Group", "has", "social", "security", "number", "544293815", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Deborah", "Ross:", "+81-586-935-1272.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Ayala-Anderson;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "timothygonzalez@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team.", "Community", "Outreach", "Division", "Chavez,", "Parker", "and", "Hall"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Leah", "Lee", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Byrd-Kaiser.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "783-01-6757.", "Phone:", "(736)", "234-2217."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Daniel", "Ruiz", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Brown-Graham.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "743-72-3978.", "Phone:", "(212)", "498-7779."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Service", "Delivery", "Team.", "Community", "Outreach", "Division", "Acosta", "Ltd"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Jeffrey", "Woods:", "+49", "790", "183", "44", "66.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Johnson", "and", "Sons;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "stephanie58@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Reginald", "Jones", "at", "+995", "962", "677", "1674", "or", "via", "email", "at", "lisa01@example.net.", "Reginald", "Jones", "works", "with", "White-Huang", "in", "South", "Kelsey."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Operations", "on", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Public", "Services", "desk", "in", "North", "Jillfort.", "The", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Public", "Services", "on", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Christina", "Hardy:", "+61-52-2335-3317.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Phillips", "and", "Sons;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "lopezglenn@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "taxpayer", "Steven", "Faulkner", "at", "Warner", "LLC", "has", "SSN", "189978814", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Jefferyshire", "on", "+61-176-787-91-61.", "Account", "manager", "Kelli", "Smith", "from", "Wright-Davis", "will", "respond", "at", "charles27@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Operations", "desk", "in", "South", "Rachelborough.", "The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Kelly", "Cole", "at", "+91", "578", "922", "3126", "or", "via", "email", "at", "jessicastanley@example.net.", "Kelly", "Cole", "works", "with", "White", "Inc", "in", "East", "Garrettville."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Community", "Outreach", "on", "the", "customer", "care", "transition.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Heatherton", "on", "00420", "795", "712", "1857.", "Account", "manager", "Megan", "Hoffman", "from", "Newton", "PLC", "will", "respond", "at", "yyoung@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Operations", "desk", "in", "Marcusfurt.", "The", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Community", "Outreach", "on", "the", "incident", "response", "drill.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Brandi", "Moody,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "462633738,", "employed", "at", "Salazar,", "Strickland", "and", "Smith."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Laura", "Bradford", "to", "824989627.", "Current", "employer:", "Joseph", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Customer", "Support", "on", "the", "incident", "response", "drill.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Amy", "Black", "(SSN:", "668-74-3805),", "who", "works", "at", "Ford", "Ltd", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(528)", "492-1969", "or", "gdavis@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Scott", "Johnson:", "+81-88-1710-9543.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Lester,", "Mcbride", "and", "Byrd;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "davidtodd@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Community", "Outreach", "desk", "in", "Lake", "Matthewberg.", "The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Compliance", "Review", "Team.", "Engineering", "Division", "Hernandez", "Group"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Russian", "taxpayer", "Kimberly", "Riley", "at", "Brown,", "Cooper", "and", "Osborne", "has", "SSN", "619913351", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Christopher", "Bennett:", "+49", "18", "4394", "4538.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Jones,", "Mcmahon", "and", "Spence;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "brooke97@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Brittany", "Stevens:", "+49", "33", "3712", "8170.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Johnson-Jones;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "lauragrant@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "French", "taxpayer", "Andre", "Alvarez", "at", "Mendoza-Singleton", "has", "SSN", "104770551", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "service", "rollout", "plan", "on", "03/10/2026", "at", "04:14.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://bowen.net/updates/372."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Patrick", "Zamora:", "+81", "37", "6781", "1797.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Bauer-Brown;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "allison14@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "German", "taxpayer", "Michelle", "White", "at", "Acosta", "LLC", "has", "SSN", "693706221", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "David", "Jennings", "at", "Cardenas,", "Brooks", "and", "Quinn", "has", "social", "security", "number", "121315004", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Community", "Outreach", "desk", "in", "Lake", "Stephen.", "The", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Engineering", "desk", "in", "West", "Michaelport.", "The", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Community", "Outreach", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Jacqueline", "Christian,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "552359209,", "employed", "at", "Wells-Martin."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Operations", "desk", "in", "Shawhaven.", "The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Martin", "Sellers", "at", "+49", "884", "597", "4145", "or", "via", "email", "at", "patrick16@example.com.", "Martin", "Sellers", "works", "with", "Haley", "Ltd", "in", "Angelhaven."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Scott", "Williams:", "+49", "562", "276", "66", "21.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Vaughn", "Inc;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "lisawoods@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "John", "Vaughn", "from", "Cross", "PLC", "was", "held", "in", "East", "Thomasland.", "Contact:", "(690)", "413-6455,", "email", "steven18@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Timothy", "Smith:", "+44", "76", "4397", "6325.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Nielsen", "LLC;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "tracy20@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Louis", "Green", "at", "+995", "355", "216", "1424", "or", "via", "email", "at", "michael76@example.org.", "Louis", "Green", "works", "with", "Baker,", "Adams", "and", "Mullen", "in", "Haynesstad."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Ann", "Ortiz", "at", "Perry-Peters", "has", "social", "security", "number", "721099460", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook", "on", "03/07/2026", "at", "10:08.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://callahan.com/updates/384."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Shawn", "Collins", "at", "+81", "63", "379", "320", "873", "or", "via", "email", "at", "gary04@example.com.", "Shawn", "Collins", "works", "with", "Reyes", "PLC", "in", "Lunahaven."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Vanessa", "Harris", "at", "Johnson", "PLC", "has", "social", "security", "number", "275642391", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Jay", "Allen", "at", "+49-631-390-2292", "or", "via", "email", "at", "robert12@example.org.", "Jay", "Allen", "works", "with", "Aguirre,", "Cohen", "and", "Mitchell", "in", "Danielmouth."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Operations", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "West", "Sarahville", "on", "+61", "66", "5668", "8355.", "Account", "manager", "Jared", "Stewart", "from", "Nunez-Nichols", "will", "respond", "at", "avilabrenda@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "George", "Pierce:", "+44", "46", "6848", "1783.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Cohen,", "Williams", "and", "Price;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "brockmadeline@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "German", "taxpayer", "Cody", "Farmer", "at", "Jensen,", "Obrien", "and", "Salazar", "has", "SSN", "732115675", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Customer", "Support", "Division", "Reed,", "Brown", "and", "Daniels"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Engineering", "Division", "Buchanan", "and", "Sons"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "South", "Donald", "on", "+995-915-381-1920.", "Account", "manager", "Ashley", "Malone", "from", "Smith", "LLC", "will", "respond", "at", "amy51@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Operations", "desk", "in", "Karenchester.", "The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Community", "Outreach", "on", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Benjamin", "Krause,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "197808626,", "employed", "at", "Bishop", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Jacob", "Williams", "at", "+61-29-9991-9647", "or", "via", "email", "at", "dharrison@example.org.", "Jacob", "Williams", "works", "with", "Holmes", "LLC", "in", "Lake", "Mariohaven."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Spanish", "employee", "Morgan", "Gordon", "MD", "at", "Mendoza-Yates", "has", "SSN", "824-43-7213", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(206)", "605-6443."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Customer", "Support", "on", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Kristin", "Garcia,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "678702179,", "employed", "at", "Bell,", "Flores", "and", "Thomas."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Government", "Support", "Team.", "Public", "Services", "Division", "Lopez-Golden"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review", "on", "02/06/2026", "at", "22:31.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://ramos.com/updates/244."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Mary", "Rivera", "at", "+995-75-470-118-471", "or", "via", "email", "at", "wbarajas@example.net.", "Mary", "Rivera", "works", "with", "Robinson-Goodwin", "in", "North", "Elizabethmouth."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "03/23/2026", "at", "10:20.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://burch-montoya.org/updates/365."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Engineering", "on", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Public", "Services", "desk", "in", "East", "Joyfurt.", "The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Engineering", "desk", "in", "North", "Amandahaven.", "The", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review", "on", "03/30/2026", "at", "07:45.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://wright.org/updates/791."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Engineering", "desk", "in", "New", "David.", "The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Customer", "Support", "desk", "in", "New", "Samanthaberg.", "The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Ryan", "Garrison:", "+44-65-8398-4743.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Garcia,", "Melton", "and", "Taylor;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "uschroeder@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Community", "Outreach", "Division", "Johnson,", "Bradford", "and", "Landry"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Andrew", "Livingston,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "478695887,", "employed", "at", "Torres,", "Glover", "and", "Green."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "West", "Lisa", "on", "+995-231-199-60-57.", "Account", "manager", "Tammy", "Moore", "from", "Stevens", "and", "Sons", "will", "respond", "at", "josephpreston@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Service", "Delivery", "Team.", "Operations", "Division", "Graves-Weaver"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Operations", "desk", "in", "South", "Eric.", "The", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "incident", "response", "drill", "on", "02/11/2026", "at", "13:56.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://williamson-cervantes.com/updates/620."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Engineering", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "02/11/2026", "at", "22:13.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://harvey.com/updates/735."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Public", "Services", "on", "the", "incident", "response", "drill.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Tyler", "Hernandez", "at", "+81", "88", "5678", "9047", "or", "via", "email", "at", "wendyatkinson@example.net.", "Tyler", "Hernandez", "works", "with", "Thompson", "Group", "in", "Kristenport."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team.", "Public", "Services", "Division", "Lewis-Lopez"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Customer", "Support", "desk", "in", "North", "Steven.", "The", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Engineering", "desk", "in", "Wilsonshire.", "The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Operations", "desk", "in", "New", "Laurie.", "The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Stephen", "Cowan:", "+61", "24", "390", "794", "794.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Ferrell-Henry;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "frederickmeadows@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Isaac", "Patterson", "at", "+91", "917", "278", "2801", "or", "via", "email", "at", "bgonzalez@example.org.", "Isaac", "Patterson", "works", "with", "Colon-Weber", "in", "Lake", "Kelly."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Michael", "Walters,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "618145490,", "employed", "at", "Mills", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "service", "rollout", "plan", "on", "03/08/2026", "at", "05:38.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://rosales.com/updates/514."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Service", "Delivery", "Team.", "Engineering", "Division", "Ali", "PLC"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Melanie", "Mosley:", "+81", "557", "143", "6776.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Olson", "LLC;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "reyeskristina@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Daniel", "Holloway:", "00420-61-525-847-197.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Washington,", "Black", "and", "Brooks;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "robertsonerik@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Joe", "Miranda", "at", "Harris,", "Spencer", "and", "Ponce", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "098-68-0698", "and", "callback", "to", "(711)", "644-6427."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Community", "Outreach", "desk", "in", "South", "Andrewland.", "The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "West", "Christopherberg", "on", "+44", "85", "3526", "3804.", "Account", "manager", "Crystal", "Hernandez", "from", "Robinson-Fisher", "will", "respond", "at", "dbolton@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Carlos", "Smith,", "a", "French", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Collins-Cox", "in", "Geraldport.", "Contact:", "(209)", "696-3236", "or", "mpreston@example.net."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Community", "Outreach", "Division", "Webster-Wolf"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Michael", "Obrien:", "+49", "928", "903", "8684.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Hubbard-Kim;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "bshort@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Public", "Services", "desk", "in", "North", "Alicebury.", "The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Alex", "Wagner", "at", "+91", "146", "325", "7475", "or", "via", "email", "at", "brooksdanielle@example.net.", "Alex", "Wagner", "works", "with", "Richardson", "Ltd", "in", "New", "Virginiaville."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Lake", "Aaron", "on", "+81-291-608-9151.", "Account", "manager", "Tara", "Holmes", "from", "Johnson", "PLC", "will", "respond", "at", "christinacraig@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team.", "Community", "Outreach", "Division", "Palmer-Brady"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Customer", "Support", "desk", "in", "Burgessburgh.", "The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Alexander", "Ryan", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Rhodes-Rosario.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "759-32-8455.", "Phone:", "(551)", "863-2791."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Customer", "Support", "on", "the", "incident", "response", "drill.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Platform", "Enablement", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "03/15/2026", "at", "23:23.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://salas.com/updates/160."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Meghan", "White", "at", "+81-863-447-4630", "or", "via", "email", "at", "timothyfreeman@example.com.", "Meghan", "White", "works", "with", "Maxwell-Carr", "in", "Williamsview."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Engineering", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Operations", "on", "the", "service", "rollout", "plan.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Engineering", "on", "the", "customer", "care", "transition.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Italian", "employee", "Thomas", "Williams", "at", "Banks,", "Smith", "and", "Chen", "has", "SSN", "399-87-8857", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(506)", "366-4939."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review", "on", "02/06/2026", "at", "13:45.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://huang.com/updates/791."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Compliance", "Review", "Team.", "Customer", "Support", "Division", "Chambers-Taylor"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "service", "rollout", "plan", "on", "03/27/2026", "at", "05:30.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://lynch.com/updates/492."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Anthony", "Hayes", "at", "+61", "838", "432", "2391", "or", "via", "email", "at", "tracygallagher@example.org.", "Anthony", "Hayes", "works", "with", "Juarez", "and", "Sons", "in", "New", "Ryan."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Lisaport", "on", "+81", "564", "617", "8048.", "Account", "manager", "Amanda", "Preston", "from", "Vaughn-Williams", "will", "respond", "at", "xmccall@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Community", "Outreach", "Division", "Moreno,", "Price", "and", "Scott"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Operations", "Division", "Johnson,", "Small", "and", "Gardner"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Community", "Outreach", "desk", "in", "South", "Shannon.", "The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "employee", "William", "Bradley", "at", "Stephens-Young", "has", "SSN", "297-30-9439", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(972)", "994-1924."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Seanview", "on", "00420", "201", "802", "7018.", "Account", "manager", "Brenda", "Mcgee", "from", "Reed", "LLC", "will", "respond", "at", "daisymccarty@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Customer", "Support", "on", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Engineering", "on", "the", "customer", "care", "transition.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Operations", "Division", "Martinez,", "Fisher", "and", "Bentley"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reach", "the", "regional", "office", "in", "Barretthaven", "on", "+91-294-881-3610.", "Account", "manager", "Amanda", "Pace", "from", "Russo", "and", "Sons", "will", "respond", "at", "washingtoncorey@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Operations", "Division", "Lam", "LLC"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review", "on", "02/07/2026", "at", "09:00.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://galloway-wyatt.com/updates/323."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Customer", "Success", "Team.", "Public", "Services", "Division", "Jenkins,", "Ortiz", "and", "Andrews"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Community", "Outreach", "desk", "in", "Mitchellside.", "The", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Russian", "employee", "Bradley", "Wagner", "at", "King-Gilbert", "has", "SSN", "101-93-7693", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(467)", "568-9401."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Operations", "desk", "in", "New", "Seanstad.", "The", "Government", "Support", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Michael", "Bell", "at", "+61-507-382-34-25", "or", "via", "email", "at", "akim@example.org.", "Michael", "Bell", "works", "with", "Le", "Inc", "in", "Snyderfurt."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Eric", "Smith", "at", "+91", "26", "8088", "9238", "or", "via", "email", "at", "wattstravis@example.com.", "Eric", "Smith", "works", "with", "Cooper", "Group", "in", "Albertchester."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Public", "Services", "desk", "in", "Phambury.", "The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Engineering", "desk", "in", "East", "Joycetown.", "The", "Compliance", "Review", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Jessica", "Brown", "at", "00420", "86", "1046", "5542", "or", "via", "email", "at", "donna43@example.org.", "Jessica", "Brown", "works", "with", "Harris-Lee", "in", "South", "Ashleyfort."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 10, 10, 10, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "feel", "free", "to", "contact", "Janice", "Combs", "at", "00420-40-2684-3399", "or", "via", "email", "at", "williamharrison@example.com.", "Janice", "Combs", "works", "with", "Mcclain,", "Salazar", "and", "Smith", "in", "North", "Karen."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 9, 0, 0, 0, 0, 11, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Gregory", "Dalton:", "00420-687-240-77-56.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Bryant", "Inc;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "astewart@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "route", "this", "request", "to", "the", "Customer", "Support", "desk", "in", "North", "Sandy.", "The", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "is", "handling", "the", "next", "update", "cycle."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Service", "Delivery", "Team.", "Operations", "Division", "Stone,", "Carpenter", "and", "Johnston"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Public", "Services", "Division", "Chapman", "and", "Sons"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Anita", "Reyes", "at", "ashleysimmons@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Salazar,", "Garrett", "and", "Perez", "is", "located", "in", "Shaneberg."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Compliance", "Review", "Team.", "Customer", "Support", "Division", "Williams", "Inc"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Service", "Delivery", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "incident", "response", "drill", "on", "02/07/2026", "at", "15:16.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://brown.com/updates/230."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Best", "regards,", "Regional", "Operations", "Team.", "Customer", "Support", "Division", "Johnson", "LLC"], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Jasmine", "Frye:", "+61-437-196-81-96.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Edwards,", "Arnold", "and", "Smith;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "james73@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Government", "Support", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Customer", "Support", "on", "the", "service", "rollout", "plan.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "will", "review", "the", "customer", "care", "transition", "on", "03/29/2026", "at", "03:41.", "Notes", "will", "be", "published", "at", "https://gonzalez.com/updates/668."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Customer", "Success", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Customer", "Support", "on", "the", "regional", "support", "handbook.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["International", "support", "callback", "for", "Alicia", "Norris:", "+44-48-4460-3248.", "Escalation", "owner", "is", "Wallace-Martinez;", "confirmation", "sent", "to", "thomas23@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 9, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-PHONE", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Shannon", "English,", "a", "Indian", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Munoz,", "Simmons", "and", "White", "in", "Jeremiahchester.", "Contact:", "(660)", "579-2514", "or", "carnold@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Michelle", "Sullivan,", "a", "Spanish", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Gardner-Bates", "in", "Maryberg.", "Contact:", "(446)", "430-5927", "or", "jtaylor@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Meeting", "summary:", "Regional", "Operations", "Team", "coordinated", "with", "Operations", "on", "the", "Q3", "readiness", "review.", "No", "customer", "data", "was", "included."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
