{"tokens": ["Employee", "Catherine", "Burch", "at", "Shaw-Oneill", "has", "social", "security", "number", "411989013", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Megan", "Hoffman", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8115687", "and", "diagnosed", "COPD.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Jose", "Campbell", "at", "phone", "number", "325471746", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Lopez", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Michelle", "Fletcher", "(MRN:", "MRN-8467726,", "DOB:", "04/03/1955).", "Admitted", "for", "Hypertension,", "treated", "with", "Warfarin", "5mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Susan", "Mendez", "to", "315779326.", "Current", "employer:", "Hill-Whitney."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "April", "Woods,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "649158694,", "employed", "at", "Wheeler", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Joseph", "Santos", "(SSN:", "721-39-8667),", "who", "works", "at", "Morton,", "Medina", "and", "Webb", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(491)", "361-8179", "or", "lpetersen@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Shannon", "Malone,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "342322064,", "employed", "at", "Sullivan", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "424501388", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Jesse", "Garza", "at", "Gray", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Jeremy", "Barnes", "to", "485916247.", "Current", "employer:", "Vaughn-Jenkins."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "269868020", "for", "Evan", "Carter", "at", "Jacobs-Foster", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jeffrey", "Roberson", "at", "Jacobs-Austin", "has", "social", "security", "number", "760548620", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Clinton", "Jensen", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2615878", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Jesse", "Rogers,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "584329486,", "employed", "at", "Ramirez-Bean."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "David", "Miles,", "MRN", "MRN-9541658,", "DOB", "02/25/1950,", "presents", "with", "COPD.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "David", "Brown", "at", "Chapman", "and", "Sons", "has", "social", "security", "number", "217735156", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Zachary", "Levy,", "MRN", "MRN-4371891.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Sertraline", "50mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Sarah", "Stevens", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2089496", "and", "diagnosed", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Cody", "Williams", "(SSN:", "043-40-5975),", "who", "works", "at", "Wilson-Jones", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(236)", "578-3426", "or", "ojones@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Frederick", "Tate", "at", "Perez", "Inc", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "619-34-0712", "and", "callback", "to", "(589)", "299-6881."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "308429884", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Dr.", "Kenneth", "Schroeder", "at", "Fitzgerald-Wyatt."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Aaron", "Cortez,", "MRN", "MRN-6663388.", "Diagnosis:", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Adjusting", "Prednisone", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Bobby", "Cook", "(MRN:", "MRN-3193891,", "DOB:", "03/05/2007).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Christina", "Morton", "at", "collinssamuel@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Murphy,", "Willis", "and", "Hines", "is", "located", "in", "East", "Christopherchester."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Cheryl", "Morgan,", "MRN", "MRN-7032283,", "DOB", "06/03/1990,", "presents", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Randy", "Shah,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "223089490,", "employed", "at", "Gates", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "534625707", "registered", "to", "Joyce", "Martinez", "at", "Stevens,", "Norris", "and", "Smith."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Emily", "Hines", "from", "Ferrell-Owens", "was", "held", "in", "Levyborough.", "Contact:", "(617)", "295-4681,", "email", "tyler16@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Kathleen", "Lynch", "(MRN:", "MRN-6020319,", "DOB:", "12/10/1991).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Shannon", "Stone", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Buchanan", "PLC.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "340-35-2040.", "Phone:", "(565)", "999-1783."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Tammie", "Hanson", "at", "Charles,", "Cortez", "and", "Evans", "has", "social", "security", "number", "485533120", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Mrs.", "Kristen", "Reyes", "(SSN:", "339-80-5144),", "who", "works", "at", "Romero,", "Suarez", "and", "Shields", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(572)", "641-2146", "or", "kendra65@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Sabrina", "Briggs,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "462327614,", "employed", "at", "Garcia", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Thomas", "Maldonado", "(MRN:", "MRN-1543335,", "DOB:", "10/23/1952).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Richard", "Jennings,", "MRN", "MRN-1262492,", "DOB", "08/28/2005,", "presents", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Current", "medication:", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Benjamin", "Mcmahon", "to", "685118577.", "Current", "employer:", "Morgan", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Rebecca", "Walker", "from", "Hill", "PLC", "was", "held", "in", "Dunnville.", "Contact:", "(653)", "877-7947,", "email", "gary79@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Marc", "Lynch", "(SSN:", "820-23-6756),", "who", "works", "at", "Garcia,", "Farmer", "and", "Garrett", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(967)", "358-4878", "or", "donna23@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Kimberly", "Rodgers", "from", "Johnson,", "Rogers", "and", "Miranda", "was", "held", "in", "Lake", "Samuel.", "Contact:", "(322)", "960-9779,", "email", "carlamoore@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Lindsay", "Moran,", "MRN", "MRN-5949685.", "Diagnosis:", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "803588039", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Crystal", "Baker", "at", "Williams", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "457486409", "registered", "to", "Cheryl", "Mclaughlin", "at", "Moss", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Michael", "Poole", "at", "Long,", "Thomas", "and", "Chen", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "685-46-1181", "and", "callback", "to", "(920)", "435-9196."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "731101345", "for", "David", "Kaufman", "at", "Black", "LLC", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Randall", "Johnson", "to", "321864177.", "Current", "employer:", "Murray,", "Erickson", "and", "Gonzales."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Kathryn", "Snyder", "(SSN:", "893-30-3653),", "who", "works", "at", "George", "Group", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(671)", "558-6000", "or", "cassandra01@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Bianca", "Carter", "at", "Howe-Long", "has", "social", "security", "number", "220447968", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Matthew", "Palmer", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-5391883", "and", "diagnosed", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Prescribed", "Prednisone", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Kayla", "Williamson,", "MRN", "MRN-6502353.", "Diagnosis:", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Debra", "Daniels", "to", "114379718.", "Current", "employer:", "Weaver-Sherman."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Stephen", "Sanford,", "MRN", "MRN-9484790,", "DOB", "06/14/1998,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "William", "Mcgee", "(MRN:", "MRN-1155477,", "DOB:", "06/12/1936).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Jacob", "Preston", "from", "Gonzales,", "Huber", "and", "Morgan", "was", "held", "in", "Lauriechester.", "Contact:", "(233)", "437-5720,", "email", "tylerjimenez@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "100577413", "for", "Kevin", "Nguyen", "at", "Hensley,", "Lopez", "and", "Baker", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Richard", "Knight", "from", "Jacobson", "Inc", "was", "held", "in", "Nelsonland.", "Contact:", "(410)", "270-4394,", "email", "jasonparrish@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Tracy", "Carter", "at", "Chen,", "Faulkner", "and", "Casey", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "234-53-5554", "and", "callback", "to", "(870)", "866-4522."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "David", "Griffith", "at", "Wilson-Herrera", "has", "social", "security", "number", "134824292", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Christina", "Herrera", "(SSN:", "589-38-4838),", "who", "works", "at", "Murphy", "PLC", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(309)", "442-7248", "or", "nwilson@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Michael", "Johnson", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-6249960", "and", "diagnosed", "COPD.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Laura", "Moore,", "MRN", "MRN-8542969,", "DOB", "06/21/1992,", "presents", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Current", "medication:", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Alexandra", "Taylor,", "MRN", "MRN-9702060.", "Diagnosis:", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "William", "Jackson,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "049316879,", "employed", "at", "Underwood", "Ltd."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Gary", "Ramirez", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2500901", "and", "diagnosed", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Cynthia", "Snyder", "at", "Spencer-Wood", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "186-75-7142", "and", "callback", "to", "(731)", "867-8245."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Jordan", "Hampton", "at", "phone", "number", "771911026", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Preston-James."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Robert", "Walker", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-3277144", "and", "diagnosed", "Hypertension.", "Prescribed", "Prednisone", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Vincent", "Rivera", "from", "Sawyer", "Group", "was", "held", "in", "South", "Monica.", "Contact:", "(782)", "508-7653,", "email", "foxstephen@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Angela", "Clark,", "MRN", "MRN-9882154,", "DOB", "04/10/1989,", "presents", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "April", "Fitzgerald", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7166363", "and", "diagnosed", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Pamela", "Romero", "at", "ericfarmer@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Harrell", "LLC", "is", "located", "in", "New", "Mariotown."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Marvin", "Greer", "at", "bryanparsons@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Marshall,", "Dominguez", "and", "Welch", "is", "located", "in", "West", "Jamesborough."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Charles", "Hill", "at", "Wright", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "578-98-9495", "and", "callback", "to", "(991)", "843-9095."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Brittney", "Martin,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "865138318,", "employed", "at", "Edwards-Martinez."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Tom", "Williams", "at", "Hamilton,", "Ramsey", "and", "Crawford", "has", "social", "security", "number", "245407685", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Brian", "Jones", "at", "phone", "number", "548656854", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Morgan-Wilson."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Yolanda", "Parsons", "from", "Mccullough,", "Hodges", "and", "Sanchez", "was", "held", "in", "Cynthiatown.", "Contact:", "(541)", "283-3317,", "email", "randolphandrew@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Joy", "Meyer", "(MRN:", "MRN-5720376,", "DOB:", "05/30/1973).", "Admitted", "for", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Ms.", "Jennifer", "Hill", "(SSN:", "303-96-5550),", "who", "works", "at", "Fry,", "Hobbs", "and", "Buck", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(368)", "463-8894", "or", "dpeters@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Kelly", "Mccoy", "at", "Norton,", "Mayo", "and", "Casey", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "142-33-0855", "and", "callback", "to", "(628)", "365-4271."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Abigail", "Owens,", "MRN", "MRN-5616316.", "Diagnosis:", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Christine", "Soto", "(MRN:", "MRN-9953163,", "DOB:", "09/17/1950).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "374159239", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Andrew", "Cruz", "at", "Mendez-Meyer."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "793420486", "for", "Tracy", "Fitzgerald", "at", "Crosby-Williams", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "307621261", "for", "Natalie", "Juarez", "at", "Johnston,", "Coleman", "and", "Scott", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Michelle", "Hodges,", "MRN", "MRN-6780235,", "DOB", "03/13/1976,", "presents", "with", "Hypertension.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Sherry", "Gibson", "to", "080419434.", "Current", "employer:", "Murphy-Smith."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Jeffrey", "Smith", "to", "280905063.", "Current", "employer:", "Harris", "Ltd."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Jonathan", "Martinez,", "MRN", "MRN-7082139.", "Diagnosis:", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Daniel", "Hunt", "at", "Jordan-Campbell", "has", "social", "security", "number", "792399838", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Julie", "Lee", "at", "Rivera", "Ltd", "has", "social", "security", "number", "422732951", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Latoya", "Miller,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "733261246,", "employed", "at", "Moore", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "024441792", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Paul", "Diaz", "at", "Ramirez-White."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Jessica", "Wilson", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-9419134", "and", "diagnosed", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Darryl", "Davis", "at", "Garcia", "LLC", "has", "social", "security", "number", "839832420", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Jennifer", "Lynch", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2882551", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Amber", "Kim", "at", "Costa-Wilkerson", "has", "social", "security", "number", "512778783", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "307219240", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Stephen", "Jones", "at", "Mcclain", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Kayla", "Hicks,", "MRN", "MRN-4553544.", "Diagnosis:", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lance", "Short", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Carter,", "Garcia", "and", "Murphy.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "558-29-2442.", "Phone:", "(470)", "840-4241."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "James", "Cooper,", "MRN", "MRN-3760475,", "DOB", "08/16/1956,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jacob", "Ramos", "(SSN:", "399-99-9570),", "who", "works", "at", "Foley", "Inc", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(625)", "263-4388", "or", "amy50@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Scott", "Johnson", "at", "davidtodd@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Lester,", "Mcbride", "and", "Byrd", "is", "located", "in", "East", "Lindsey."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Jeff", "Owens", "to", "599559561.", "Current", "employer:", "Brown,", "Valdez", "and", "Lucas."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Alicia", "Lewis", "at", "Dunn", "Ltd", "has", "social", "security", "number", "645880879", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Carmen", "Rose", "from", "Henderson,", "Lewis", "and", "Ryan", "was", "held", "in", "Samuelhaven.", "Contact:", "(855)", "904-4598,", "email", "jenniferross@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Kelly", "Hartman", "(MRN:", "MRN-8944327,", "DOB:", "10/14/1946).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Ann", "Williams", "at", "Hernandez", "and", "Sons", "has", "social", "security", "number", "234994742", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jaime", "Bowman,", "MRN", "MRN-9460003,", "DOB", "06/14/1991,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Shelley", "Quinn", "to", "064581696.", "Current", "employer:", "Wise", "Inc."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Colton", "Figueroa", "at", "Key,", "Mendoza", "and", "Sanchez", "has", "social", "security", "number", "575429996", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Matthew", "Obrien,", "MRN", "MRN-2373555,", "DOB", "08/24/1958,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Charles", "Clark", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Trujillo", "PLC.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "783-33-4743.", "Phone:", "(409)", "508-4460."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "586672779", "registered", "to", "Dale", "Heath", "at", "Cohen,", "Serrano", "and", "Jacobs."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Alicia", "Smith,", "MRN", "MRN-9367799,", "DOB", "09/14/1988,", "presents", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Kayla", "Rodriguez", "at", "stephen00@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Walker,", "Gilbert", "and", "Acosta", "is", "located", "in", "Simmonsville."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jordan", "Moore", "(SSN:", "245-17-7759),", "who", "works", "at", "Walker-Rodriguez", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(453)", "404-1333", "or", "danny49@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Theodore", "Jones", "Jr.", "at", "Hernandez,", "Martinez", "and", "Weber", "has", "social", "security", "number", "439187565", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Natalie", "Ortiz", "(MRN:", "MRN-7435310,", "DOB:", "09/18/1953).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Bruce", "Brown,", "MRN", "MRN-6068298.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Sertraline", "50mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Mr.", "James", "Brown", "(MRN:", "MRN-1710601,", "DOB:", "12/05/1992).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Michael", "Anderson", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-1137194", "and", "diagnosed", "Hypertension.", "Prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Brenda", "Morrison,", "MRN", "MRN-4446065.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Barry", "Bernard", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Webster", "and", "Sons.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "598-73-8566.", "Phone:", "(240)", "834-2343."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "320447461", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Robert", "Mendoza", "at", "Johnson,", "Reed", "and", "Dalton."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Danielle", "Wheeler", "(SSN:", "781-23-8318),", "who", "works", "at", "Miller,", "Sandoval", "and", "Cunningham", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(939)", "936-5315", "or", "sarah35@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Susan", "Arroyo,", "MRN", "MRN-3872269,", "DOB", "10/26/2000,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Patricia", "Morrow", "from", "Martinez", "LLC", "was", "held", "in", "Port", "Kimberly.", "Contact:", "(293)", "681-6700,", "email", "coleerin@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Nathaniel", "Lee", "(MRN:", "MRN-9453969,", "DOB:", "11/30/1967).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Timothy", "Walls", "at", "jonesjason@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Ellis", "PLC", "is", "located", "in", "West", "Nicole."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Samantha", "Davis", "at", "May", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "361-39-6390", "and", "callback", "to", "(983)", "789-7232."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Anthony", "Hoffman", "at", "Tran-Jones", "has", "social", "security", "number", "614662237", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Vanessa", "Thompson,", "MRN", "MRN-4655777.", "Diagnosis:", "Hypertension.", "Adjusting", "Metformin", "500mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Amber", "Charles", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8731427", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Lisa", "Haynes", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-9712957", "and", "diagnosed", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Prescribed", "Amoxicillin", "250mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Matthew", "Bates", "to", "764715420.", "Current", "employer:", "Larson", "Inc."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Nicholas", "Olson,", "MRN", "MRN-2681042.", "Diagnosis:", "COPD.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Travis", "Joyce,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "184390232,", "employed", "at", "Hammond-Strickland."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "327388045", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Rebecca", "Mendez", "at", "Mann,", "Martin", "and", "Oconnell."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Ann", "Phillips", "at", "Perry,", "Gonzalez", "and", "Buchanan", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "562-58-2608", "and", "callback", "to", "(936)", "716-7991."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jason", "Marshall", "(SSN:", "716-63-1990),", "who", "works", "at", "Lawson-Edwards", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(762)", "334-5719", "or", "jessica56@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Maria", "Jones", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Grant", "Group.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "314-85-9529.", "Phone:", "(501)", "426-7625."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Ian", "Frazier,", "MRN", "MRN-1781180,", "DOB", "05/10/1959,", "presents", "with", "Hypertension.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jack", "Galloway", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Allen-Allen.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "168-60-6217.", "Phone:", "(850)", "375-9751."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Isaac", "Patterson", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Colon-Weber.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "260-96-0267.", "Phone:", "(681)", "244-7338."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Jeremy", "Horne", "MD", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7241348", "and", "diagnosed", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Jennifer", "Evans", "at", "melissaturner@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Webster", "Group", "is", "located", "in", "Port", "Steven."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Jessica", "Perez,", "MRN", "MRN-5105957.", "Diagnosis:", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Adjusting", "Albuterol", "inhaler", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Laura", "Thompson", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-9608154", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "172564522", "registered", "to", "Joseph", "Perez", "at", "Clarke-James."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Jeremy", "Jones,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "041565281,", "employed", "at", "Moreno", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Holly", "Chapman", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-4931560", "and", "diagnosed", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Yolanda", "Mendoza", "at", "amy49@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Edwards-Thompson", "is", "located", "in", "East", "Joshua."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "523968500", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Hayden", "Shannon", "at", "White-Reese."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Melissa", "Williams,", "MRN", "MRN-4162177.", "Diagnosis:", "Hypertension.", "Adjusting", "Metformin", "500mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Jasmine", "Dixon", "(MRN:", "MRN-8728009,", "DOB:", "04/26/1993).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "780351675", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Mr.", "Daniel", "Martin", "at", "Johnson-Williams."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Elizabeth", "Brown,", "MRN", "MRN-4609524,", "DOB", "06/27/1938,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Tamara", "Sanchez,", "MRN", "MRN-1864641,", "DOB", "01/23/1938,", "presents", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Current", "medication:", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Dan", "Dougherty", "at", "david76@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Duran", "LLC", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Amanda."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Lisa", "Hensley", "at", "Lee,", "Jones", "and", "Stanley", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "007-98-2616", "and", "callback", "to", "(425)", "659-5557."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Kyle", "Johnson", "(SSN:", "529-16-4671),", "who", "works", "at", "Brown-Frey", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(580)", "767-2680", "or", "katie32@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Jay", "Mcneil", "to", "772833132.", "Current", "employer:", "Harris-Carson."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Timothy", "Carlson,", "MRN", "MRN-9315137.", "Diagnosis:", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Elizabeth", "Ward", "(SSN:", "310-84-6690),", "who", "works", "at", "Owens-Lang", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(863)", "264-8606", "or", "ugill@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Jamie", "Montoya,", "MRN", "MRN-8010946.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Metformin", "500mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Hector", "Norton", "from", "Watson", "Group", "was", "held", "in", "Gabriellaland.", "Contact:", "(482)", "394-3001,", "email", "scunningham@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Richard", "Graham", "from", "Wilson,", "Lam", "and", "Lee", "was", "held", "in", "West", "Ryan.", "Contact:", "(232)", "538-2160,", "email", "fletcheraaron@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Shelly", "Phelps,", "MRN", "MRN-3540594.", "Diagnosis:", "COPD.", "Adjusting", "Sertraline", "50mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Andrew", "Dunn", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-5774152", "and", "diagnosed", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Prescribed", "Prednisone", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Kristen", "Davis", "from", "Murray", "Inc", "was", "held", "in", "Robertfort.", "Contact:", "(394)", "460-1727,", "email", "tyronemoran@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Andrea", "Young", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Washington,", "Ryan", "and", "Cummings.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "659-59-2341.", "Phone:", "(871)", "711-7482."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Logan", "Maxwell", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7370211", "and", "diagnosed", "COPD.", "Prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Joshua", "Gibson", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Curry,", "Baker", "and", "James.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "731-37-3842.", "Phone:", "(841)", "444-5499."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Mrs.", "Maria", "Williams", "(SSN:", "503-58-0283),", "who", "works", "at", "Kim,", "Gonzales", "and", "Mills", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(976)", "446-8800", "or", "michaelhardin@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Melanie", "Wells,", "MRN", "MRN-5791184,", "DOB", "10/22/1944,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "John", "Adams", "at", "sonia96@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Thomas", "Inc", "is", "located", "in", "Port", "Mark."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jessica", "Smith", "(SSN:", "895-86-6930),", "who", "works", "at", "Walker-Burgess", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(775)", "537-3002", "or", "seanmyers@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Amber", "Campbell", "at", "Khan,", "Pena", "and", "Ruiz", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "280-54-7906", "and", "callback", "to", "(710)", "933-5781."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Erin", "Carter", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7987842", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Michael", "Paul", "to", "418438891.", "Current", "employer:", "Barnes,", "Newton", "and", "Moore."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Kimberly", "Mitchell", "at", "Li,", "Craig", "and", "Drake", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "661-46-0993", "and", "callback", "to", "(571)", "301-7018."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Thomas", "Ellis,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "301815926,", "employed", "at", "Taylor-Mcgee."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Nancy", "Stewart", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Davis", "LLC.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "045-94-8544.", "Phone:", "(662)", "715-4629."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Kelly", "Watts,", "MRN", "MRN-1851702,", "DOB", "04/13/1980,", "presents", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Current", "medication:", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Scott", "Wilson", "to", "452059496.", "Current", "employer:", "Long,", "Anderson", "and", "Irwin."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Scott", "Sanchez", "to", "290506698.", "Current", "employer:", "Cox-Mora."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Ryan", "Parker", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Ruiz-Jacobson.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "644-14-9534.", "Phone:", "(269)", "553-4950."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Laura", "Williams", "from", "Graves-Weaver", "was", "held", "in", "West", "Robertberg.", "Contact:", "(963)", "708-5689,", "email", "michaelcesar@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Tracey", "Walsh", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-9459284", "and", "diagnosed", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Kari", "Lee", "to", "633071337.", "Current", "employer:", "Maynard-Wagner."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "474306637", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Dr.", "Samuel", "Holmes", "DDS", "at", "Evans-Hart."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Tyler", "Cooper", "at", "phone", "number", "069390733", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Jimenez", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "809491212", "registered", "to", "Ronald", "Herman", "at", "Bailey-Ochoa."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Brittany", "Gay", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8792046", "and", "diagnosed", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Alexandra", "Fisher,", "MRN", "MRN-1652868.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Laura", "Chang", "at", "phillipslucas@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Martin", "Inc", "is", "located", "in", "West", "Georgefurt."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Sheryl", "Acosta,", "MRN", "MRN-5872986,", "DOB", "04/01/2000,", "presents", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "817381134", "registered", "to", "Crystal", "Jackson", "at", "Ward", "Ltd."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Alexander", "Williams,", "MRN", "MRN-5675638,", "DOB", "06/24/1997,", "presents", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Current", "medication:", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Mr.", "Thomas", "Miller", "at", "Thomas,", "Collins", "and", "Gibson", "has", "social", "security", "number", "592653486", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Joshua", "Ruiz", "at", "Pham,", "Petersen", "and", "Gill", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "310-26-6303", "and", "callback", "to", "(634)", "906-5097."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Erica", "Ramos", "at", "Lewis,", "Kennedy", "and", "Santana", "has", "social", "security", "number", "746441791", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Douglas", "Baker", "(MRN:", "MRN-9745141,", "DOB:", "11/24/1946).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Derek", "Floyd,", "MRN", "MRN-2346371,", "DOB", "12/12/2006,", "presents", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Cynthia", "Martin", "at", "Keith", "Inc", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "383-57-8480", "and", "callback", "to", "(930)", "519-7537."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Andrew", "Gonzales", "at", "Perez-Adams", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "834-83-2869", "and", "callback", "to", "(336)", "245-6772."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Chase", "Baker", "at", "Jones", "and", "Sons", "has", "social", "security", "number", "040613645", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Heather", "Jones", "from", "Quinn", "Ltd", "was", "held", "in", "North", "Michael.", "Contact:", "(802)", "639-6003,", "email", "ingramjill@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Michael", "Powell", "(MRN:", "MRN-1962308,", "DOB:", "02/16/1992).", "Admitted", "for", "Hypertension,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Andrew", "Gonzales", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Robinson,", "Shields", "and", "Brown.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "375-68-8222.", "Phone:", "(405)", "335-9837."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Kristen", "Robinson", "(MRN:", "MRN-8663806,", "DOB:", "06/17/1950).", "Admitted", "for", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Javier", "Mercado", "(MRN:", "MRN-6007984,", "DOB:", "04/29/1947).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "011134240", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Michael", "Nicholson", "at", "Spencer", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "852942322", "for", "Sheila", "Henry", "at", "Ramirez,", "Walker", "and", "Ray", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Julie", "Johnson", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Mann-Warner.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "422-86-4066.", "Phone:", "(383)", "954-6442."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jonathan", "Phillips,", "MRN", "MRN-4052834,", "DOB", "05/09/2001,", "presents", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Current", "medication:", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Patrick", "Bonilla", "at", "vbarnes@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Reese", "and", "Sons", "is", "located", "in", "Larrymouth."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Mr.", "Matthew", "Steele,", "MRN", "MRN-1158547.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Cynthia", "Brown,", "MRN", "MRN-2237331,", "DOB", "09/25/1997,", "presents", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Thomas", "Weaver", "DDS", "at", "duranrobert@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Warren", "Inc", "is", "located", "in", "North", "Jasmine."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Joseph", "Hanson,", "MRN", "MRN-3920762,", "DOB", "10/26/1977,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Gabrielle", "Davis", "at", "Howard", "LLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "575-26-8929", "and", "callback", "to", "(423)", "438-9279."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Matthew", "Velez", "from", "Pearson", "and", "Sons", "was", "held", "in", "Port", "Randyfort.", "Contact:", "(292)", "644-2612,", "email", "gentrygregory@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Jesus", "Obrien", "from", "Taylor,", "Velazquez", "and", "Flores", "was", "held", "in", "Williamhaven.", "Contact:", "(489)", "943-5891,", "email", "vewing@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Richard", "Gibson", "at", "smoore@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Horton-Cross", "is", "located", "in", "New", "Jillton."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Angela", "Hernandez,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "714949106,", "employed", "at", "Benson-Mccarthy."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "David", "Davenport", "to", "367319648.", "Current", "employer:", "Rhodes-Fernandez."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jon", "Martin,", "MRN", "MRN-5819172,", "DOB", "01/02/1990,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Robert", "Contreras", "at", "Larson,", "Dodson", "and", "Vance", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "772-31-2725", "and", "callback", "to", "(867)", "753-1241."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Robert", "Torres", "at", "eddie35@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Terry,", "Williams", "and", "Huff", "is", "located", "in", "Lake", "Kentburgh."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Thomas", "Webb,", "MRN", "MRN-6851946,", "DOB", "09/06/1976,", "presents", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Rachel", "Leon", "at", "Simpson", "Inc", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "643-41-2474", "and", "callback", "to", "(897)", "778-6295."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Deanna", "Medina", "at", "phone", "number", "810478797", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Wright,", "Ramos", "and", "Bennett."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Justin", "Riley", "to", "507422980.", "Current", "employer:", "Glass,", "Cunningham", "and", "Reid."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Paul", "Larsen", "(SSN:", "061-22-6210),", "who", "works", "at", "Cannon-Boyd", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(697)", "692-4502", "or", "joshuajones@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Madison", "Marshall,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "155306276,", "employed", "at", "Turner,", "Ortiz", "and", "Taylor."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Lisa", "Kennedy,", "MRN", "MRN-5990112,", "DOB", "05/09/1949,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Mark", "Roberts", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Smith-Nguyen.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "446-23-8549.", "Phone:", "(570)", "850-8532."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "158492528", "registered", "to", "Haley", "Sparks", "at", "Smith,", "Macias", "and", "Gonzales."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Brian", "Harris", "at", "Ortiz", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "520-71-0334", "and", "callback", "to", "(269)", "738-9914."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Linda", "Campbell,", "MRN", "MRN-1440972.", "Diagnosis:", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Jacqueline", "Cooper", "(MRN:", "MRN-8711874,", "DOB:", "06/18/1943).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Warfarin", "5mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Sara", "Harris,", "MRN", "MRN-7033835,", "DOB", "08/25/1995,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Brittney", "Campbell,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "581111404,", "employed", "at", "Robbins", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Leslie", "Bell,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "611904527,", "employed", "at", "Collins", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Roberto", "Bartlett", "(MRN:", "MRN-5952504,", "DOB:", "11/27/1964).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Amy", "Silva", "at", "Calhoun,", "Schmidt", "and", "Brown", "has", "social", "security", "number", "446217434", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Tyler", "Vasquez", "at", "phone", "number", "354047910", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Duran", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "David", "Douglas", "Jr.", "(SSN:", "877-71-1605),", "who", "works", "at", "Osborne", "and", "Sons", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(455)", "277-8260", "or", "lindadominguez@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Justin", "Russell,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "491526985,", "employed", "at", "Davis", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Melissa", "Thompson", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7976731", "and", "diagnosed", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Kelly", "Haynes", "to", "687558332.", "Current", "employer:", "Ellis-Adkins."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Erica", "Daniel,", "MRN", "MRN-5960015.", "Diagnosis:", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Adjusting", "Prednisone", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Mary", "Bryant,", "MRN", "MRN-2889899.", "Diagnosis:", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "365716151", "registered", "to", "Rebecca", "Hughes", "at", "Keith-Williams."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "248332526", "registered", "to", "Kelly", "Mclaughlin", "at", "Calhoun", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Anthony", "Johnson,", "MRN", "MRN-8351320,", "DOB", "11/04/1938,", "presents", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Current", "medication:", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "106041469", "for", "Nathan", "Stanley", "at", "Valentine-Robinson", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Kimberly", "Valdez", "at", "phone", "number", "394972293", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Diaz", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "006407287", "for", "Ruth", "Guerrero", "at", "Shepherd-Cortez", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Donna", "Jennings,", "MRN", "MRN-3348114,", "DOB", "06/06/1979,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Veronica", "Ferguson", "at", "Vargas-Alvarado", "has", "social", "security", "number", "191099750", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Peter", "Perez", "(SSN:", "065-92-7499),", "who", "works", "at", "Randall", "PLC", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(912)", "690-3986", "or", "rsheppard@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Alfred", "Galvan", "at", "Santos,", "Moody", "and", "Taylor", "has", "social", "security", "number", "053337828", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "441849739", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Jennifer", "Bowers", "at", "White-Hansen."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Brent", "Hopkins,", "MRN", "MRN-8175669.", "Diagnosis:", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jerry", "Christensen", "(SSN:", "107-18-4334),", "who", "works", "at", "Bishop,", "Gray", "and", "Johnson", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(883)", "767-5905", "or", "hunter35@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Courtney", "Walker", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2362693", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Rachael", "Johnson", "at", "michael90@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Young", "Ltd", "is", "located", "in", "Lake", "Shannon."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "791879644", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Dale", "Wright", "at", "Kelly,", "Maxwell", "and", "Wilson."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Mark", "Copeland", "to", "865143987.", "Current", "employer:", "Martinez", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Janet", "Williams", "at", "Walker-Velasquez", "has", "social", "security", "number", "022769076", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
