{"tokens": ["Lance", "Short", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Carter,", "Garcia", "and", "Murphy.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "484-32-7484.", "Phone:", "(721)", "922-5479."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Mark", "Roberts", "at", "xcollier@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Smith-Nguyen", "is", "located", "in", "Richardbury."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Thomas", "Mccann", "(Italian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-5960015.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "prescribed", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Susan", "Mendez,", "a", "Brazilian", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Hill-Whitney", "in", "North", "Douglas.", "Contact:", "(592)", "395-9327", "or", "jonesdana@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Cristian", "Santos", "at", "Barnes,", "Cole", "and", "Ramirez", "has", "social", "security", "number", "239659864", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Christina", "Weaver", "from", "Cervantes-Garcia", "presented", "passport", "number", "E65243509", "at", "the", "border."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Pamela", "Henderson", "(MRN:", "MRN-2324175,", "DOB:", "07/17/1964).", "Admitted", "for", "COPD,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "555450158", "for", "Joyce", "Martinez", "at", "Stevens,", "Norris", "and", "Smith", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Justin", "Barnett", "to", "549983034.", "Current", "employer:", "Jones-Hensley."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Gina", "Wilson", "from", "Taylor", "and", "Sons", "was", "held", "in", "Christopherfurt.", "Contact:", "(678)", "330-9751,", "email", "zcoffey@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Christian", "Neal", "authorized", "payment", "via", "7853-9907-1602-6890", "for", "services", "from", "Smith,", "Fisher", "and", "Garcia."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Mexican", "patient", "Evan", "Lamb,", "MRN", "MRN-5014486,", "DOB", "10/22/1979,", "presented", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Started", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Alejandra", "King", "authorized", "payment", "via", "9000-4015-9882-1962", "for", "services", "from", "Marquez-Fletcher."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Dale", "Heath", "at", "phone", "number", "434906591", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Cohen,", "Serrano", "and", "Jacobs."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tammy", "Anderson", "at", "Santos,", "Mullen", "and", "Gordon:", "passport", "Z17966873,", "last", "login", "from", "146.90.137.72."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0, 21], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O", "B-IPV4"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Justin", "Riley", "at", "michelle52@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Glass,", "Cunningham", "and", "Reid", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Scottport."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Login", "from", "232.167.43.14", "by", "Lisa", "Avila", "flagged.", "Notify", "Williams,", "Charles", "and", "Howard", "security", "at", "robertsgina@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 21, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Kari", "Lee", "from", "Maynard-Wagner", "was", "held", "in", "Burnsland.", "Contact:", "(858)", "536-3093,", "email", "fortiz@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Katelyn", "Stewart", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7370211", "and", "diagnosed", "COPD.", "Prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Matthew", "Lamb,", "MRN", "MRN-8895137,", "DOB", "11/21/1941,", "presents", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "John", "Adams", "at", "Thomas", "Inc", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "510-75-2345", "and", "callback", "to", "(379)", "280-7267."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Michael", "Paul", "(SSN:", "359-29-1125),", "who", "works", "at", "Barnes,", "Newton", "and", "Moore", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(283)", "681-1317", "or", "fpena@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Debit", "card", "9019964661347367", "linked", "to", "Denise", "Cruz", "at", "Marsh-Banks.", "Call", "(533)", "401-8496", "to", "verify."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 9, 10, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Adam", "Clark", "(MRN:", "MRN-9010256,", "DOB:", "10/11/1985).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Tiffany", "Sanders,", "MRN", "MRN-7163058.", "Diagnosis:", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "James", "Simmons", "MD,", "MRN", "MRN-4265774.", "Diagnosis:", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Adjusting", "Atorvastatin", "20mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Brian", "Martin", "at", "jcervantes@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Steele-Roberts", "is", "located", "in", "Millerview."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "German", "employee", "Michael", "Poole", "at", "Long,", "Thomas", "and", "Chen", "has", "SSN", "804-61-3179", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(439)", "746-4918."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Jacob", "Preston", "at", "tylerjimenez@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Gonzales,", "Huber", "and", "Morgan", "is", "located", "in", "Lauriechester."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Login", "from", "186.180.194.60", "by", "Preston", "Kim", "flagged.", "Notify", "Short-Johnson", "security", "at", "amandataylor@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 21, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Jennifer", "Vaughn", "at", "phone", "number", "518186462", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Lewis", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Debit", "card", "6671354155164088", "linked", "to", "Shane", "Buchanan", "at", "Matthews,", "Harrington", "and", "Rodriguez.", "Call", "(744)", "588-4762", "to", "verify."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 9, 10, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Patricia", "Morrow", "at", "coleerin@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Martinez", "LLC", "is", "located", "in", "Port", "Kimberly."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Alexandra", "Rogers", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-3083077", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jason", "Williams", "from", "Pena-Smith", "presented", "passport", "number", "U33251181", "at", "the", "border."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Oscar", "Parker", "(MRN:", "MRN-6413349,", "DOB:", "02/26/1950).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Warfarin", "5mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Bobby", "Cook", "at", "Edwards", "Inc.", "Card:", "5419-2674-3170-2430.", "Contact:", "(293)", "205-6050."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "751704017", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Sheila", "Henry", "at", "Ramirez,", "Walker", "and", "Ray."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Steven", "Rogers", "(MRN:", "MRN-2289923,", "DOB:", "07/08/1966).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Warfarin", "5mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Charge", "2130-8734-1519-5703", "for", "the", "subscription", "renewal.", "Account", "holder:", "Megan", "Oliver", "at", "Avery", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "patient", "Vickie", "Price,", "MRN", "MRN-4817541,", "DOB", "06/13/2003,", "presented", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Started", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Paul", "Larsen", "at", "Cannon-Boyd", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "414-16-9334", "and", "callback", "to", "(390)", "270-2113."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Jessica", "Smith,", "a", "Mexican", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Walker-Burgess", "in", "West", "Whitney.", "Contact:", "(577)", "493-2257", "or", "seanmyers@example.net."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Mark", "Jimenez,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "333084807,", "employed", "at", "Gardner,", "May", "and", "Turner."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Debit", "card", "8319537464005947", "linked", "to", "Brendan", "Long", "at", "Larsen,", "Hernandez", "and", "Ward.", "Call", "(454)", "206-5272", "to", "verify."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 9, 10, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Login", "from", "156.131.49.192", "by", "Kelly", "Gallegos", "flagged.", "Notify", "Baker,", "Stephens", "and", "Thompson", "security", "at", "pdiaz@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 21, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Tammy", "Allison", "to", "740934316.", "Current", "employer:", "Russell", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Crystal", "Jackson", "at", "phone", "number", "377214180", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Ward", "Ltd."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Visa", "card", "1998386979999120", "on", "file", "for", "Patrick", "Mccall", "at", "Smith-Roth."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Chinese", "citizen", "Jennifer", "Evans", "at", "Webster", "Group.", "SSN:", "234-53-5554,", "callback", "(870)", "866-4522."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jennifer", "Donaldson,", "MRN", "MRN-7227905,", "DOB", "05/23/1995,", "presents", "with", "Hypertension.", "Current", "medication:", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "057649288", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Samuel", "Galvan", "at", "Mitchell,", "Johnson", "and", "Greene."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Gary", "Mendez,", "MRN", "MRN-9816043.", "Diagnosis:", "COPD.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Julian", "Conner", "at", "Cole", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "122-72-6819", "and", "callback", "to", "(352)", "776-5978."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Sarah", "Townsend", "(Italian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-5557052.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Mark", "Copeland,", "MRN", "MRN-8568671,", "DOB", "05/13/1936,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Keith", "Aguilar", "at", "Buckley", "PLC.", "Card:", "7868-1256-4943-4376.", "Contact:", "(983)", "315-1527."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Login", "from", "193.32.151.187", "by", "Kimberly", "Valdez", "flagged.", "Notify", "Diaz", "and", "Sons", "security", "at", "dennis88@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 21, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Todd", "Johnson,", "MRN", "MRN-4058117.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "William", "Grant", "(SSN:", "675-51-4498),", "who", "works", "at", "Fischer-Gonzalez", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(788)", "502-5837", "or", "cporter@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Theodore", "Jones", "Jr.", "at", "Hernandez,", "Martinez", "and", "Weber", "has", "social", "security", "number", "519835591", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Passport", "S45882178", "verified", "for", "Charles", "Santiago", "traveling", "on", "behalf", "of", "Adams", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 23, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Emily", "Hines", "to", "010604713.", "Current", "employer:", "Ferrell-Owens."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Raymond", "Shannon,", "MRN", "MRN-2975701.", "Diagnosis:", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Adjusting", "Atorvastatin", "20mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Credit", "card", "number", "6890487120172936", "belongs", "to", "Edward", "Stanley.", "Employer:", "Castillo,", "Davis", "and", "Clark."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "British", "citizen", "Kimberly", "Mitchell", "at", "Li,", "Craig", "and", "Drake.", "SSN:", "221-49-6879,", "callback", "(958)", "848-1502."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Cynthia", "Rowe", "at", "Flores", "Group", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "789-14-6966", "and", "callback", "to", "(871)", "904-1090."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Henry", "Santiago", "at", "Zuniga,", "Wong", "and", "Lynch", "has", "social", "security", "number", "271067528", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Andrew", "Cruz", "at", "phone", "number", "270929448", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Mendez-Meyer."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "751160481", "for", "Rebecca", "Mendez", "at", "Mann,", "Martin", "and", "Oconnell", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Login", "from", "221.182.157.162", "by", "Pamela", "Hill", "flagged.", "Notify", "Waller-Chavez", "security", "at", "devonmorrison@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 21, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Ann", "Phillips", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Perry,", "Gonzalez", "and", "Buchanan.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "399-44-6625.", "Phone:", "(699)", "424-5471."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Sarah", "Hawkins", "(MRN:", "MRN-8015136,", "DOB:", "05/03/1975).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Rebecca", "Horton", "from", "Beck,", "House", "and", "Hughes", "presented", "passport", "number", "W27809465", "at", "the", "border."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Amber", "Flynn", "at", "amandaknight@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Howard-Jordan", "is", "located", "in", "East", "Christian."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Russian", "patient", "Frank", "Campbell", "MD,", "MRN", "MRN-3689594,", "DOB", "09/16/1944,", "presented", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Started", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Amber", "Morales,", "MRN", "MRN-7189302,", "DOB", "03/14/1999,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Rachel", "Lane", "at", "phone", "number", "251127119", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Meyer", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Mexican", "employee", "Daniel", "Hunt", "at", "Jordan-Campbell", "has", "SSN", "485-71-8699", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(908)", "449-6016."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Kirk", "Thompson", "at", "Matthews-Bailey.", "Card:", "8635-2615-8692-6246.", "Contact:", "(467)", "568-9401."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Charge", "2562-4027-3303-8822", "for", "the", "subscription", "renewal.", "Account", "holder:", "Colton", "Terry", "at", "Frost,", "Fernandez", "and", "Guerrero."], "ner_tags": [0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Jason", "Marshall", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Lawson-Edwards.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "580-88-2951.", "Phone:", "(583)", "641-3385."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "James", "Griffin", "at", "Finley-Turner", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "869-59-1502", "and", "callback", "to", "(262)", "607-5520."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Erika", "Chavez,", "MRN", "MRN-9102469.", "Diagnosis:", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Adjusting", "Albuterol", "inhaler", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Mary", "Walker", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2089496", "and", "diagnosed", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Credit", "card", "number", "5911893322606916", "belongs", "to", "Michael", "Sims.", "Employer:", "Perez", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Australian", "taxpayer", "Jeremy", "Jones", "at", "Moreno", "Group", "has", "SSN", "566988904", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Justin", "Mullen", "to", "449578587.", "Current", "employer:", "Salinas", "Ltd."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Brazilian", "patient", "Robert", "Campbell,", "MRN", "MRN-6020319,", "DOB", "03/17/1994,", "presented", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Started", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Shannon", "Mcdowell", "(MRN:", "MRN-6625238,", "DOB:", "12/27/1941).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Kevin", "Stone", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-4986941", "and", "diagnosed", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "James", "Combs", "(MRN:", "MRN-6568772,", "DOB:", "11/24/1965).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Joshua", "Fitzpatrick,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "026809199,", "employed", "at", "Nelson,", "Rodriguez", "and", "Yang."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Robert", "Contreras", "from", "Larson,", "Dodson", "and", "Vance", "was", "held", "in", "Lake", "Michelle.", "Contact:", "(251)", "798-8811,", "email", "jrivas@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Kevin", "Warner", "(MRN:", "MRN-2843740,", "DOB:", "11/06/1960).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Metformin", "500mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Rebecca", "Walker", "to", "372402954.", "Current", "employer:", "Hill", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Korean", "citizen", "Wayne", "Powell", "at", "Bryan,", "Smith", "and", "Booth.", "SSN:", "671-42-7619,", "callback", "(493)", "415-8043."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Erin", "Carter", "from", "Moreno,", "Barajas", "and", "Colon", "presented", "passport", "number", "Z81729237", "at", "the", "border."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "375702831", "registered", "to", "David", "White", "at", "Greene-Elliott."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Kathy", "Walsh,", "MRN", "MRN-6664316,", "DOB", "12/18/1963,", "presents", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Kristin", "Haney,", "a", "Chinese", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Armstrong", "and", "Sons", "in", "Trevorland.", "Contact:", "(906)", "570-2443", "or", "rjackson@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jeffrey", "Smith", "(SSN:", "347-87-9796),", "who", "works", "at", "Harris", "Ltd", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(572)", "581-5634", "or", "raylauren@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Spanish", "patient", "Amy", "Wade,", "MRN", "MRN-3684131,", "DOB", "03/20/1983,", "presented", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Started", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Brandon", "Davis", "(MRN:", "MRN-3508522,", "DOB:", "10/03/1950).", "Admitted", "for", "COPD,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Elizabeth", "Marshall", "MD", "at", "Sawyer", "LLC.", "Card:", "2791-3692-4996-9454.", "Contact:", "(927)", "317-1370."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "002986165", "for", "Kevin", "Nguyen", "at", "Hensley,", "Lopez", "and", "Baker", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "David", "Griffith", "at", "Wilson-Herrera", "has", "social", "security", "number", "719146268", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Mexican", "patient", "Mrs.", "Tonya", "Kaufman,", "MRN", "MRN-2323049,", "DOB", "07/27/1945,", "presented", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Started", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Kayla", "Rodriguez", "(SSN:", "825-16-9273),", "who", "works", "at", "Walker,", "Gilbert", "and", "Acosta", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(304)", "913-5941", "or", "stephen00@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Jennifer", "Bowers", "at", "phone", "number", "013912249", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "White-Hansen."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Debit", "card", "8501382658732388", "linked", "to", "Ashley", "Horton", "at", "Jarvis", "and", "Sons.", "Call", "(601)", "801-2871", "to", "verify."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 9, 10, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Kenneth", "Perez", "at", "phone", "number", "729361525", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Le", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Credit", "card", "number", "6620846043899537", "belongs", "to", "Aaron", "Powers.", "Employer:", "Conley", "Ltd."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Rebecca", "Wright,", "MRN", "MRN-9541658,", "DOB", "09/30/2007,", "presents", "with", "COPD.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Isaac", "Turner", "at", "Ferguson,", "Hill", "and", "Mccann", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "359-40-3729", "and", "callback", "to", "(681)", "427-4269."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Mikayla", "Silva", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Warren", "Ltd.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "035-75-5978.", "Phone:", "(842)", "861-1645."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Larry", "Carey", "at", "phone", "number", "285115078", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Banks,", "Boyd", "and", "Wood."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "William", "Oconnor", "(Italian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-5587856.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Anna", "Lozano", "at", "gbrown@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Wilkerson-Arias", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Virginia."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Karen", "Perez", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-9993490", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Maria", "Porter", "(MRN:", "MRN-2993318,", "DOB:", "08/15/1999).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Brandy", "Carrillo,", "MRN", "MRN-2224284.", "Diagnosis:", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Mario", "Barber", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-1088100", "and", "diagnosed", "Hypertension.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Credit", "card", "number", "1402890927125840", "belongs", "to", "Andrew", "Crawford.", "Employer:", "Watts", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Samantha", "Sanders", "at", "Smith", "Ltd.", "Card:", "7114-1990-8916-8993.", "Contact:", "(354)", "209-4583."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Lisa", "Hensley", "at", "Lee,", "Jones", "and", "Stanley", "has", "social", "security", "number", "782441675", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Matthew", "Bowers,", "MRN", "MRN-1703065.", "Diagnosis:", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Adjusting", "Atorvastatin", "20mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Amy", "Bates", "(Italian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-5440189.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "William", "Davidson", "at", "Green-Dawson.", "Card:", "3937-2753-2578-9591.", "Contact:", "(714)", "914-8054."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "David", "Davenport", "to", "210393461.", "Current", "employer:", "Rhodes-Fernandez."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Charge", "7236-8639-9743-6886", "for", "the", "subscription", "renewal.", "Account", "holder:", "Kathy", "Reid", "at", "Maldonado", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Donald", "Juarez", "authorized", "payment", "via", "1430-2468-6798-2524", "for", "services", "from", "Johnston", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Debit", "card", "4625339012655272", "linked", "to", "Steven", "Curry", "at", "Davis,", "Johnson", "and", "Williams.", "Call", "(579)", "520-7781", "to", "verify."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 9, 10, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Charge", "4365-9008-2489-9361", "for", "the", "subscription", "renewal.", "Account", "holder:", "Jennifer", "Avila", "at", "Spencer", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Credit", "card", "number", "6807537975022294", "belongs", "to", "Elizabeth", "Hernandez.", "Employer:", "Yoder", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Veronica", "Ferguson,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "071326055,", "employed", "at", "Vargas-Alvarado."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Jessica", "Larsen", "at", "Frazier", "LLC:", "passport", "U29173414,", "last", "login", "from", "18.136.145.3."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0, 21], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O", "B-IPV4"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Brandon", "Thomas", "at", "phone", "number", "827554457", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Graham,", "Brown", "and", "Walker."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Melanie", "Morales", "authorized", "payment", "via", "6253-4881-5944-3347", "for", "services", "from", "Preston-Rivera."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Juan", "Jordan", "(SSN:", "061-30-1105),", "who", "works", "at", "Parker", "Inc", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(802)", "425-1117", "or", "jason31@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Gregory", "Lewis,", "MRN", "MRN-9511546.", "Diagnosis:", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Adjusting", "Albuterol", "inhaler", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Kevin", "Ford", "at", "Ruiz", "Ltd.", "Card:", "6666-1879-2600-8161.", "Contact:", "(941)", "280-9204."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Lindsey", "Lewis,", "MRN", "MRN-2781470,", "DOB", "09/15/1997,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Login", "from", "211.194.11.195", "by", "Natalie", "Ortiz", "flagged.", "Notify", "Carr-Lopez", "security", "at", "ylewis@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 21, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Jennifer", "Nichols", "authorized", "payment", "via", "8484-1945-8575-6049", "for", "services", "from", "Armstrong-Young."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Jamie", "Baird,", "a", "German", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Blevins-Ballard", "in", "Julieborough.", "Contact:", "(292)", "604-1228", "or", "bobby15@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Kimberly", "Rodgers", "to", "811819664.", "Current", "employer:", "Johnson,", "Rogers", "and", "Miranda."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jeffrey", "Hawkins", "at", "Martin", "LLC", "connected", "from", "192.72.178.240.", "Email:", "riverajenna@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 21, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Passport", "F46778269", "verified", "for", "Susan", "Russell", "traveling", "on", "behalf", "of", "Mccoy-Hamilton."], "ner_tags": [0, 23, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Jeffrey", "Moody", "(MRN:", "MRN-2739191,", "DOB:", "04/06/1953).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Joseph", "Diaz", "(MRN:", "MRN-6007984,", "DOB:", "06/20/1940).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Visa", "card", "9972928143129792", "on", "file", "for", "Brittany", "Horton", "at", "Miller", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jesse", "Rogers", "at", "Ramirez-Bean", "has", "social", "security", "number", "827848667", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Riley", "Bryant", "(SSN:", "411-98-9013),", "who", "works", "at", "Copeland", "Group", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(537)", "621-9117", "or", "chenbailey@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Amber", "Wilson", "authorized", "payment", "via", "7932-7176-2211-8357", "for", "services", "from", "James-Kelley."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Kelly", "Moody", "at", "Harrison-Gibson", "connected", "from", "218.217.169.225.", "Email:", "williamsdeborah@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 21, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Ann", "Williams", "at", "Hernandez", "and", "Sons", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "167-48-5821", "and", "callback", "to", "(589)", "484-8428."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Visa", "card", "2218559398971539", "on", "file", "for", "Katie", "Bruce", "at", "Walter,", "White", "and", "Davis."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "401761084", "for", "Natalie", "Juarez", "at", "Johnston,", "Coleman", "and", "Scott", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Anthony", "Anderson,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "809319648,", "employed", "at", "Bryant-Brown."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Debit", "card", "5067681637251725", "linked", "to", "Lisa", "Haynes", "at", "Rivas-Garcia.", "Call", "(749)", "808-2392", "to", "verify."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 9, 10, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Ray", "Walsh", "to", "347039639.", "Current", "employer:", "Martin-Ramos."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Visa", "card", "3527738361886909", "on", "file", "for", "William", "Orozco", "at", "Thomas-Huffman."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Lisa", "Ramos", "(German", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-1730386.", "Diagnosed", "with", "COPD,", "prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Samuel", "Howe", "(MRN:", "MRN-1508113,", "DOB:", "11/11/1963).", "Admitted", "for", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Charge", "4621-8303-7129-7408", "for", "the", "subscription", "renewal.", "Account", "holder:", "Dennis", "Mills", "at", "Howard", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Login", "from", "127.105.176.126", "by", "Gary", "Ramirez", "flagged.", "Notify", "Walker,", "Schneider", "and", "Powell", "security", "at", "christianwallace@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 21, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Italian", "citizen", "Jordan", "Moore", "at", "Walker-Rodriguez.", "SSN:", "389-44-0471,", "callback", "(449)", "968-8613."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Adam", "Taylor", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8351320", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Amoxicillin", "250mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Christine", "Lawson", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-1620485", "and", "diagnosed", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Sylvia", "Jones,", "MRN", "MRN-6920597.", "Diagnosis:", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Adjusting", "Metformin", "500mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "524272546", "for", "Joseph", "Perez", "at", "Clarke-James", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Frederick", "Tate", "at", "Perez", "Inc", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "883-47-9460", "and", "callback", "to", "(587)", "280-5803."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Charge", "1797-5009-1724-7590", "for", "the", "subscription", "renewal.", "Account", "holder:", "Rachel", "Dillon", "at", "Humphrey-Baker."], "ner_tags": [0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Kimberly", "Hernandez", "(Japanese", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-6389033.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Hypertension,", "prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Korean", "citizen", "Amy", "Silva", "at", "Calhoun,", "Schmidt", "and", "Brown.", "SSN:", "001-77-5311,", "callback", "(980)", "365-9837."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Brazilian", "taxpayer", "Emily", "Collins", "at", "Hays-Daniels", "has", "SSN", "565029049", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Barry", "Bernard", "from", "Webster", "and", "Sons", "was", "held", "in", "South", "Elizabeth.", "Contact:", "(883)", "767-5905,", "email", "maryhowell@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Charge", "4971-6339-7161-5592", "for", "the", "subscription", "renewal.", "Account", "holder:", "Danny", "Mercer", "at", "Gross", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Henry", "Pugh", "MD", "at", "Willis,", "James", "and", "Barton", "has", "social", "security", "number", "573865803", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Thomas", "Weaver", "DDS,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "720985063,", "employed", "at", "Warren", "Inc."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "French", "employee", "Nicole", "Thompson", "at", "Prince,", "Wilcox", "and", "Robertson", "has", "SSN", "102-88-6019", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(422)", "654-8285."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Brazilian", "citizen", "Rita", "Ponce", "DVM", "at", "Reed,", "Brown", "and", "Daniels.", "SSN:", "391-50-2493,", "callback", "(525)", "962-8749."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Autumn", "Wilson", "at", "Jimenez", "PLC.", "Card:", "6432-8052-2735-1172.", "Contact:", "(860)", "893-7547."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Cody", "Reid,", "a", "Canadian", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Ellison,", "Arias", "and", "Thompson", "in", "Harveystad.", "Contact:", "(871)", "915-7421", "or", "tracytaylor@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Jennifer", "Gomez", "at", "phone", "number", "184298451", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Smith,", "Collier", "and", "Wright."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Sherry", "Gibson,", "MRN", "MRN-8391997.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Atorvastatin", "20mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Allison", "Weaver,", "MRN", "MRN-4052834,", "DOB", "08/07/1981,", "presents", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Current", "medication:", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Jason", "Jackson", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-1625760", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Michael", "Young", "(SSN:", "273-19-1170),", "who", "works", "at", "Bishop-Goodwin", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(635)", "317-9922", "or", "pyoung@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Ashley", "Richardson", "(MRN:", "MRN-5886733,", "DOB:", "01/08/1957).", "Admitted", "for", "COPD,", "treated", "with", "Metformin", "500mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Shelly", "Spencer,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "041565281,", "employed", "at", "Dawson", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Patrick", "Smith,", "MRN", "MRN-4599894,", "DOB", "11/11/1997,", "presents", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "French", "patient", "Brandon", "Reyes,", "MRN", "MRN-6688907,", "DOB", "10/12/1965,", "presented", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Started", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Leslie", "Bell", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Collins", "Group.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "591-81-0879.", "Phone:", "(689)", "316-2070."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "German", "employee", "David", "Brown", "at", "Chapman", "and", "Sons", "has", "SSN", "439-75-6544", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(452)", "962-9830."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Charge", "5833-4164-3875-7643", "for", "the", "subscription", "renewal.", "Account", "holder:", "Matthew", "Lawson", "at", "Moore-Garcia."], "ner_tags": [0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Robin", "Wheeler", "at", "Rodriguez", "and", "Sons", "has", "social", "security", "number", "473580617", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Donald", "Jones", "from", "Bell-Hicks", "was", "held", "in", "Benjaminchester.", "Contact:", "(299)", "874-8062,", "email", "sheila14@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Michael", "Simmons", "at", "Davis", "Inc.", "Card:", "8570-4798-7636-4022.", "Contact:", "(765)", "363-6422."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Dana", "Richardson,", "MRN", "MRN-2237331,", "DOB", "02/14/2006,", "presents", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Courtney", "Walker", "authorized", "payment", "via", "9856-6435-7288-3292", "for", "services", "from", "Fisher-Eaton."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "German", "taxpayer", "Justin", "Russell", "at", "Davis", "PLC", "has", "SSN", "022422816", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Sara", "Carpenter", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Burns,", "Hernandez", "and", "Ryan.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "507-52-3998.", "Phone:", "(624)", "844-4185."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "American", "taxpayer", "Marc", "Lynch", "at", "Garcia,", "Farmer", "and", "Garrett", "has", "SSN", "445455140", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Amanda", "Jones", "at", "hamiltoncorey@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Cohen,", "Mitchell", "and", "Perez", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Garrettport."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Gabrielle", "Davis", "to", "604360107.", "Current", "employer:", "Howard", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Marvin", "Greer", "from", "Marshall,", "Dominguez", "and", "Welch", "was", "held", "in", "West", "Jamesborough.", "Contact:", "(978)", "252-4335,", "email", "bryanparsons@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Mexican", "taxpayer", "Brandon", "Simmons", "at", "Scott,", "Mckay", "and", "Mcdaniel", "has", "SSN", "828697922", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Paul", "Marks,", "MRN", "MRN-3574265.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Melissa", "Stewart", "at", "phone", "number", "465799976", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Rodriguez-Simmons."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Richard", "Knight", "from", "Jacobson", "Inc", "was", "held", "in", "Nelsonland.", "Contact:", "(877)", "634-8957,", "email", "jasonparrish@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Russian", "patient", "Christopher", "Smith,", "MRN", "MRN-4590102,", "DOB", "06/04/1986,", "presented", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Started", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Michelle", "Olson", "at", "Mendoza-Garza", "connected", "from", "228.251.4.253.", "Email:", "cjohnson@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 21, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Brazilian", "taxpayer", "Brittney", "Campbell", "at", "Robbins", "and", "Sons", "has", "SSN", "688846119", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Charge", "7887-7135-7266-8348", "for", "the", "subscription", "renewal.", "Account", "holder:", "William", "Stanton", "at", "Martinez", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Claudia", "Lyons", "to", "216925618.", "Current", "employer:", "Jackson-Lawson."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Nathaniel", "Johnson", "at", "Short,", "Brooks", "and", "Lang", "connected", "from", "145.219.125.202.", "Email:", "stucker@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 21, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Robin", "Gray,", "MRN", "MRN-6811015.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Atorvastatin", "20mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Olivia", "Harris", "from", "Anderson,", "Roberts", "and", "Gilmore", "was", "held", "in", "Lake", "Eric.", "Contact:", "(652)", "891-4501,", "email", "omartinez@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Melissa", "Montgomery", "at", "Stanley-Wright", "connected", "from", "216.116.159.14.", "Email:", "elizabeth62@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 21, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Glenn", "Gallegos", "at", "Kelley-Brooks:", "passport", "R78559218,", "last", "login", "from", "29.147.30.69."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0, 21], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O", "B-IPV4"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "509598369", "for", "Linda", "Bautista", "at", "Bowman", "Group", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Angela", "Hernandez,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "674759261,", "employed", "at", "Benson-Mccarthy."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Chelsea", "Lewis", "at", "Figueroa-Malone.", "Card:", "3196-7363-4978-5177.", "Contact:", "(775)", "622-7824."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Janet", "Williams", "from", "Walker-Velasquez", "was", "held", "in", "North", "Donna.", "Contact:", "(940)", "784-8744,", "email", "ybailey@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Matthew", "Velez", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Pearson", "and", "Sons.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "119-13-3847.", "Phone:", "(343)", "246-1609."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Francisco", "Taylor", "at", "Rios", "LLC.", "Card:", "4700-5914-2320-1519.", "Contact:", "(615)", "670-4984."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "William", "Barry", "(MRN:", "MRN-6547958,", "DOB:", "08/09/1986).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Australian", "employee", "Gregory", "Hill", "at", "Cannon,", "Johnson", "and", "Keller", "has", "SSN", "455-10-1324", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(636)", "902-2768."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Brianna", "Dennis", "at", "Williams-Juarez:", "passport", "U21307671,", "last", "login", "from", "64.142.154.154."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0, 21], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O", "B-IPV4"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "German", "patient", "Laura", "Chang,", "MRN", "MRN-5856449,", "DOB", "08/23/1951,", "presented", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Started", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Steven", "Ellis", "(Canadian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-2567468.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "prescribed", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Credit", "card", "number", "6697294339249802", "belongs", "to", "Michael", "Harris.", "Employer:", "Hernandez,", "Larson", "and", "Flores."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Alexandra", "Le", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Dyer,", "Potter", "and", "Mack.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "547-94-4011.", "Phone:", "(886)", "473-2169."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Paul", "Brennan", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Mcdowell-Smith.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "714-70-6867.", "Phone:", "(597)", "664-7078."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "taxpayer", "Charles", "Clark", "at", "Trujillo", "PLC", "has", "SSN", "710992713", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Robert", "Baxter", "(Mexican", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-5035998.", "Diagnosed", "with", "COPD,", "prescribed", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Mrs.", "Maria", "Williams", "at", "michaelhardin@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Kim,", "Gonzales", "and", "Mills", "is", "located", "in", "Schroederton."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Spanish", "employee", "Julie", "Lee", "at", "Rivera", "Ltd", "has", "SSN", "418-36-0537", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(624)", "870-2622."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Donald", "Evans", "to", "348295457.", "Current", "employer:", "Ward", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Thomas", "Hamilton,", "MRN", "MRN-7765480,", "DOB", "01/23/1988,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Randy", "Hayes", "(MRN:", "MRN-3410360,", "DOB:", "12/31/1968).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Warfarin", "5mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Joseph", "Santos", "at", "Morton,", "Medina", "and", "Webb", "has", "social", "security", "number", "078892443", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Courtney", "Gonzalez", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Williams", "Group.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "749-72-7974.", "Phone:", "(599)", "471-8454."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Grace", "Reeves", "at", "Nichols,", "Glover", "and", "Knox.", "Card:", "2562-9653-1697-4764.", "Contact:", "(644)", "860-6427."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "607731021", "registered", "to", "Mark", "Cole", "at", "Green-Ward."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Eric", "Patrick", "from", "Johnson", "LLC", "was", "held", "in", "New", "Greg.", "Contact:", "(819)", "687-9214,", "email", "byrdfrank@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Jacob", "Ramos", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Foley", "Inc.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "637-20-3909.", "Phone:", "(972)", "231-5051."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "American", "patient", "Carrie", "Young", "MD,", "MRN", "MRN-7378535,", "DOB", "01/21/1989,", "presented", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Started", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jessica", "Hall", "at", "Schneider,", "Lewis", "and", "Lopez:", "passport", "P61792685,", "last", "login", "from", "29.62.128.164."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0, 21], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O", "B-IPV4"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "171482080", "for", "Nicole", "Griffin", "at", "Avery,", "Garcia", "and", "Romero", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Joshua", "Ruiz", "to", "891305384.", "Current", "employer:", "Pham,", "Petersen", "and", "Gill."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Korean", "citizen", "Shannon", "Malone", "at", "Sullivan", "Group.", "SSN:", "691-11-4459,", "callback", "(253)", "359-3579."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Pamela", "Thompson,", "a", "Chinese", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Pearson,", "Moon", "and", "White", "in", "Baileymouth.", "Contact:", "(882)", "618-6344", "or", "fwalters@example.org."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Mr.", "Carl", "Rios", "at", "Mitchell", "Inc", "connected", "from", "27.81.95.226.", "Email:", "louishayes@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 21, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-IPV4", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Hunter", "Silva", "(MRN:", "MRN-6029651,", "DOB:", "03/02/1952).", "Admitted", "for", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis,", "treated", "with", "Metformin", "500mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Credit", "card", "number", "2025266797964063", "belongs", "to", "Sherry", "Davis.", "Employer:", "White-Morales."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Tyler", "Johnson", "(MRN:", "MRN-8467726,", "DOB:", "10/21/1993).", "Admitted", "for", "Hypertension,", "treated", "with", "Warfarin", "5mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Danielle", "Burke,", "MRN", "MRN-6679880.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Prednisone", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "062518301", "for", "Kevin", "Saunders", "at", "Keller,", "Baker", "and", "Ramsey", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "184059059", "registered", "to", "Brian", "Jones", "at", "Morgan-Wilson."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Australian", "patient", "Brian", "Leon,", "MRN", "MRN-6246485,", "DOB", "01/16/1944,", "presented", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Started", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Veronica", "Brewer", "(SSN:", "463-65-3630),", "who", "works", "at", "Brooks-Vance", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(687)", "659-6931", "or", "ykane@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Diana", "Daniels", "at", "brendagoodwin@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Johnson,", "Mcfarland", "and", "Edwards", "is", "located", "in", "Hickmanport."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Heather", "Bennett", "(Canadian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-1609681.", "Diagnosed", "with", "COPD,", "prescribed", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Barbara", "Dawson", "authorized", "payment", "via", "9939-3947-1440-8563", "for", "services", "from", "Brooks", "Ltd."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Leslie", "Powers,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "680195732,", "employed", "at", "Wilson-Torres."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "French", "taxpayer", "Randy", "Shah", "at", "Gates", "PLC", "has", "SSN", "135864916", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Australian", "employee", "Mr.", "Thomas", "Miller", "at", "Thomas,", "Collins", "and", "Gibson", "has", "SSN", "586-84-3085", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(673)", "794-1672."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "758803975", "registered", "to", "Tyler", "Vasquez", "at", "Duran", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Kathryn", "Snyder,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "869164921,", "employed", "at", "George", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lisa", "Smith", "at", "Wagner", "Group:", "passport", "A75043108,", "last", "login", "from", "35.50.209.99."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0, 21], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O", "B-IPV4"]}
{"tokens": ["Passport", "N92688322", "verified", "for", "Stephanie", "Atkinson", "traveling", "on", "behalf", "of", "Johnson,", "Perkins", "and", "Sullivan."], "ner_tags": [0, 23, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Debit", "card", "2916399971163316", "linked", "to", "Thomas", "Webb", "at", "Gregory,", "White", "and", "James.", "Call", "(337)", "520-2931", "to", "verify."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 19, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 9, 10, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Todd", "Byrd", "to", "096973873.", "Current", "employer:", "Gilbert", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Juan", "Harding", "at", "Scott-Underwood", "has", "social", "security", "number", "232559191", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jamie", "Solomon", "from", "Sullivan,", "Roth", "and", "Reed", "presented", "passport", "number", "J96727439", "at", "the", "border."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 23, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PASSPORT", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Jeffrey", "Roberson", "to", "510967056.", "Current", "employer:", "Jacobs-Austin."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "007530392", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Robert", "Mendoza", "at", "Johnson,", "Reed", "and", "Dalton."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "230424068", "registered", "to", "Deanna", "Medina", "at", "Wright,", "Ramos", "and", "Bennett."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Process", "refund", "for", "Travis", "Chan", "Jr.", "at", "Garcia,", "Scott", "and", "Hall.", "Card:", "8412-6225-2100-5919.", "Contact:", "(556)", "687-2599."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 19, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-CREDIT_CARD", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
