{"tokens": ["Patient", "Joseph", "Watts,", "MRN", "MRN-9929043,", "DOB", "01/18/1971,", "presents", "with", "COPD.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Ann", "Phillips", "at", "alyssa42@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Perry,", "Gonzalez", "and", "Buchanan", "is", "located", "in", "Coffeyport."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Kimberly", "Rodgers", "(SSN:", "832-35-2245),", "who", "works", "at", "Johnson,", "Rogers", "and", "Miranda", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(806)", "907-4978", "or", "carlamoore@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Jessica", "Mays", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7370211", "and", "diagnosed", "COPD.", "Prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Alicia", "Norris", "from", "Wallace-Martinez", "was", "held", "in", "West", "Robertville.", "Contact:", "(219)", "462-4533,", "email", "thomas23@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Yolanda", "Mendoza", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Edwards-Thompson.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "356-13-2496.", "Phone:", "(434)", "890-1339."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Mr.", "Scott", "Williams", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-3503456", "and", "diagnosed", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Veronica", "Brewer", "at", "ykane@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Brooks-Vance", "is", "located", "in", "Lake", "Tamaraside."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Michael", "Clements", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Bryan-Velasquez.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "400-35-1717.", "Phone:", "(404)", "242-6170."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Shannon", "Anderson,", "MRN", "MRN-4184887.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Prednisone", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Adriana", "Macias,", "MRN", "MRN-1652868.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Kathryn", "Snyder", "from", "George", "Group", "was", "held", "in", "Port", "Emilyview.", "Contact:", "(989)", "333-5291,", "email", "cassandra01@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Sabrina", "Briggs", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Garcia", "LLC.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "987-69-3977.", "Phone:", "(251)", "466-7211."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Joseph", "Santos", "at", "Morton,", "Medina", "and", "Webb", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "182-33-2122", "and", "callback", "to", "(809)", "269-4853."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Jared", "Stewart", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Nunez-Nichols.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "655-47-5914.", "Phone:", "(361)", "928-3852."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Rachael", "Johnson", "from", "Young", "Ltd", "was", "held", "in", "Lake", "Shannon.", "Contact:", "(322)", "960-9779,", "email", "michael90@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Lance", "Montoya,", "MRN", "MRN-6502353.", "Diagnosis:", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Scott", "Sanchez", "at", "sarahmathews@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Cox-Mora", "is", "located", "in", "Walkerbury."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Latoya", "Miller", "at", "craigjoseph@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Moore", "PLC", "is", "located", "in", "Tuckermouth."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Lauren", "Hammond,", "MRN", "MRN-8542969,", "DOB", "09/01/1950,", "presents", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Current", "medication:", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "John", "Adams", "from", "Thomas", "Inc", "was", "held", "in", "Port", "Mark.", "Contact:", "(876)", "283-3573,", "email", "sonia96@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Julie", "Lee", "at", "Rivera", "Ltd", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "523-16-4073", "and", "callback", "to", "(730)", "570-9167."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Jason", "Marshall", "from", "Lawson-Edwards", "was", "held", "in", "Zacharyville.", "Contact:", "(824)", "957-2625,", "email", "jessica56@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Justin", "Russell", "at", "carlsonkristen@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Davis", "PLC", "is", "located", "in", "West", "Robertland."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Cynthia", "Snyder", "(SSN:", "666-47-3068),", "who", "works", "at", "Spencer-Wood", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(853)", "970-9042", "or", "cherylmiller@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Brian", "Brown", "at", "Davidson-Hensley", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "473-96-4891", "and", "callback", "to", "(654)", "825-5668."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Richard", "Graham", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Wilson,", "Lam", "and", "Lee.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "993-87-7932.", "Phone:", "(416)", "752-4295."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Latoya", "Brown", "(MRN:", "MRN-9705660,", "DOB:", "12/18/1989).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Steven", "Greene", "(MRN:", "MRN-9123194,", "DOB:", "03/19/1999).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "William", "Espinoza", "(MRN:", "MRN-7439870,", "DOB:", "03/24/1963).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Krista", "Barber,", "MRN", "MRN-8808032.", "Diagnosis:", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Mr.", "Thomas", "Miller", "(SSN:", "219-27-1742),", "who", "works", "at", "Thomas,", "Collins", "and", "Gibson", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(238)", "511-9071", "or", "adrianabailey@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Tammie", "Hanson", "(SSN:", "508-95-7118),", "who", "works", "at", "Charles,", "Cortez", "and", "Evans", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(648)", "729-8397", "or", "elizabeth56@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Scott", "Johnson", "at", "Lester,", "Mcbride", "and", "Byrd", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "761-32-1641", "and", "callback", "to", "(453)", "924-8172."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jessica", "Smith", "at", "Walker-Burgess", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "326-92-2035", "and", "callback", "to", "(850)", "675-5951."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Travis", "Joyce", "(SSN:", "538-94-7071),", "who", "works", "at", "Hammond-Strickland", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(270)", "718-6590", "or", "mburch@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Alicia", "Lewis", "at", "Dunn", "Ltd", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "972-41-2419", "and", "callback", "to", "(485)", "661-4995."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Marvin", "Greer", "at", "Marshall,", "Dominguez", "and", "Welch", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "187-40-7658", "and", "callback", "to", "(700)", "768-4937."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Elizabeth", "Cannon,", "MRN", "MRN-9882154,", "DOB", "05/22/1993,", "presents", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Scott", "Parsons,", "MRN", "MRN-4162177.", "Diagnosis:", "Hypertension.", "Adjusting", "Metformin", "500mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Christina", "Christensen", "(SSN:", "557-15-6776),", "who", "works", "at", "Terrell", "Ltd", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(829)", "645-5498", "or", "dwayne04@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Michael", "Rivera,", "MRN", "MRN-3652149.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Albuterol", "inhaler", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Thomas", "Lin", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8731427", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Mr.", "James", "Kramer,", "MRN", "MRN-4446065.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Barry", "Bernard", "at", "maryhowell@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Webster", "and", "Sons", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Elizabeth."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Kristen", "Davis", "(SSN:", "867-29-4878),", "who", "works", "at", "Murray", "Inc", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(366)", "381-7755", "or", "tyronemoran@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Matthew", "Bates", "from", "Larson", "Inc", "was", "held", "in", "Lake", "Ellenhaven.", "Contact:", "(820)", "821-2876,", "email", "angelica52@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Mercedes", "Baker", "(MRN:", "MRN-8663806,", "DOB:", "02/10/1956).", "Admitted", "for", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Timothy", "Walls", "(SSN:", "798-78-5371),", "who", "works", "at", "Ellis", "PLC", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(987)", "856-6573", "or", "jonesjason@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Randall", "Johnson", "(SSN:", "474-21-7464),", "who", "works", "at", "Murray,", "Erickson", "and", "Gonzales", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(214)", "470-9791", "or", "marie16@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Richard", "Knight", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Jacobson", "Inc.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "175-66-6661.", "Phone:", "(801)", "506-7951."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Brian", "Lee", "(MRN:", "MRN-6271120,", "DOB:", "06/17/1937).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Margaret", "Mcfarland,", "MRN", "MRN-4504577,", "DOB", "12/05/1965,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Jasmine", "Burns", "(MRN:", "MRN-5889688,", "DOB:", "09/07/1980).", "Admitted", "for", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Alyssa", "Lee", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Hood", "and", "Sons.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "470-12-6940.", "Phone:", "(516)", "384-4509."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Mrs.", "Kristen", "Reyes", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Romero,", "Suarez", "and", "Shields.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "283-52-7745.", "Phone:", "(885)", "952-5065."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Melissa", "Mitchell", "(SSN:", "402-22-9317),", "who", "works", "at", "Williams-Nash", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(989)", "752-9626", "or", "mercedesholland@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Robin", "Wheeler", "at", "gabriel90@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Rodriguez", "and", "Sons", "is", "located", "in", "Rasmussenmouth."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Veronica", "Ferguson", "at", "Vargas-Alvarado", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "956-11-2528", "and", "callback", "to", "(971)", "442-3724."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Samantha", "Davis", "at", "May", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "725-19-8461", "and", "callback", "to", "(624)", "844-4185."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Joshua", "Ruiz", "at", "Pham,", "Petersen", "and", "Gill", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "961-24-8560", "and", "callback", "to", "(320)", "863-3522."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jeffrey", "Smith", "(SSN:", "770-22-9017),", "who", "works", "at", "Harris", "Ltd", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(830)", "617-5583", "or", "raylauren@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Louis", "Ford,", "MRN", "MRN-2221118.", "Diagnosis:", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Adjusting", "Sertraline", "50mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Benjamin", "Mcmahon", "at", "bbush@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Morgan", "PLC", "is", "located", "in", "New", "Pamela."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Alexandria", "Oneill", "(SSN:", "359-12-6850),", "who", "works", "at", "Saunders,", "Ray", "and", "Cunningham", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(269)", "553-4950", "or", "april91@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Theodore", "Jones", "Jr.", "at", "Hernandez,", "Martinez", "and", "Weber", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "783-77-6198", "and", "callback", "to", "(973)", "653-9270."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Dean", "Shannon,", "MRN", "MRN-1849015.", "Diagnosis:", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Adjusting", "Albuterol", "inhaler", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Kimberly", "Krause", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8546170", "and", "diagnosed", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Kari", "Lee", "from", "Maynard-Wagner", "was", "held", "in", "Burnsland.", "Contact:", "(251)", "541-4990,", "email", "fortiz@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jack", "White", "at", "Peterson", "Group", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "418-23-1420", "and", "callback", "to", "(519)", "789-7149."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Ann", "Williams", "at", "ycarlson@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Hernandez", "and", "Sons", "is", "located", "in", "Riceside."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Frederick", "Tate", "(SSN:", "259-37-6514),", "who", "works", "at", "Perez", "Inc", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(304)", "294-7224", "or", "richard13@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Juan", "Grant,", "MRN", "MRN-5819172,", "DOB", "03/08/1948,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Linda", "Valencia", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-9273246", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Emily", "Hines", "at", "Ferrell-Owens", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "277-80-2229", "and", "callback", "to", "(360)", "202-7693."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Alexandra", "Le", "(SSN:", "296-18-1750),", "who", "works", "at", "Dyer,", "Potter", "and", "Mack", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(877)", "433-5741", "or", "daniel62@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Joshua", "Gibson", "from", "Curry,", "Baker", "and", "James", "was", "held", "in", "Rosebury.", "Contact:", "(676)", "652-8244,", "email", "daniel37@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Paul", "Brennan", "at", "Mcdowell-Smith", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "891-61-9431", "and", "callback", "to", "(201)", "873-9889."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Ryan", "Parker", "at", "Ruiz-Jacobson", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "708-74-7299", "and", "callback", "to", "(673)", "794-1672."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jane", "Short,", "MRN", "MRN-3329967,", "DOB", "05/21/1937,", "presents", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Laura", "Chang", "at", "Martin", "Inc", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "758-91-6295", "and", "callback", "to", "(842)", "523-3473."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Michael", "Young,", "MRN", "MRN-3872269,", "DOB", "12/14/1955,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Lauren", "Foster,", "MRN", "MRN-3587398.", "Diagnosis:", "COPD.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Marc", "Lynch", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Garcia,", "Farmer", "and", "Garrett.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "999-27-5333.", "Phone:", "(318)", "309-3546."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Kelly", "Mccoy", "at", "Norton,", "Mayo", "and", "Casey", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "953-95-6802", "and", "callback", "to", "(273)", "606-1693."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Diana", "Daniels", "from", "Johnson,", "Mcfarland", "and", "Edwards", "was", "held", "in", "Hickmanport.", "Contact:", "(593)", "694-2747,", "email", "brendagoodwin@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Brian", "Harris", "at", "Ortiz", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "157-55-9312", "and", "callback", "to", "(275)", "517-8565."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Michelle", "Brock", "(MRN:", "MRN-9745141,", "DOB:", "09/05/1975).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Jerry", "Christensen", "at", "hunter35@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Bishop,", "Gray", "and", "Johnson", "is", "located", "in", "Joshuaview."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Cristian", "Santos", "(SSN:", "242-23-9935),", "who", "works", "at", "Barnes,", "Cole", "and", "Ramirez", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(289)", "804-7912", "or", "blakeerik@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Michael", "Jacobs,", "MRN", "MRN-5278117,", "DOB", "03/31/1977,", "presents", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Pamela", "Romero", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Harrell", "LLC.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "975-39-2654.", "Phone:", "(589)", "484-8428."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Jeremy", "Jones", "at", "debra31@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Moreno", "Group", "is", "located", "in", "South", "April."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Amanda", "Miller", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-4009069", "and", "diagnosed", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dennis", "Huffman", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Church,", "Edwards", "and", "Price.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "806-57-4559.", "Phone:", "(654)", "655-4868."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Molly", "Hansen", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Arroyo", "LLC.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "614-77-7859.", "Phone:", "(365)", "404-3267."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Eric", "Gutierrez,", "MRN", "MRN-9484790,", "DOB", "07/03/1946,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Nichole", "Miranda,", "MRN", "MRN-6956059.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Metformin", "500mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Steven", "Friedman", "at", "ian66@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Johns-Davis", "is", "located", "in", "Maryfort."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Lee", "Schwartz", "at", "shawn22@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Hill", "LLC", "is", "located", "in", "Meganside."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Thomas", "Ellis", "at", "julie69@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Taylor-Mcgee", "is", "located", "in", "Jeffreyberg."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Catherine", "Burch", "at", "Shaw-Oneill", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "288-16-5136", "and", "callback", "to", "(689)", "316-2070."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Randy", "Shah", "at", "Gates", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "649-67-3296", "and", "callback", "to", "(632)", "387-5563."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Isaac", "Turner", "(SSN:", "650-37-9288),", "who", "works", "at", "Ferguson,", "Hill", "and", "Mccann", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(471)", "335-6718", "or", "heidi27@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Curtis", "Smith,", "MRN", "MRN-7032283,", "DOB", "07/02/1986,", "presents", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Jason", "Morris", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8385715", "and", "diagnosed", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Vincent", "Rivera", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Sawyer", "Group.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "775-34-7528.", "Phone:", "(536)", "485-2137."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jesse", "Chavez,", "MRN", "MRN-7362994,", "DOB", "04/09/1986,", "presents", "with", "COPD.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Angela", "Harrington", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Morgan-Schwartz.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "459-92-9346.", "Phone:", "(609)", "895-9785."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Nicole", "Meyer", "(MRN:", "MRN-9953163,", "DOB:", "01/04/1968).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Tom", "Williams", "from", "Hamilton,", "Ramsey", "and", "Crawford", "was", "held", "in", "East", "Joshua.", "Contact:", "(709)", "964-8055,", "email", "lvega@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jaime", "Lang", "(SSN:", "319-88-5678),", "who", "works", "at", "Tucker-Phillips", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(910)", "702-4279", "or", "lukemiller@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Jeremy", "Barnes", "at", "vsalas@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Vaughn-Jenkins", "is", "located", "in", "Lake", "Devinborough."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Maureen", "Hernandez", "at", "conwaydawn@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Chan", "Inc", "is", "located", "in", "Josephton."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Lisa", "Hensley", "at", "tracie31@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Lee,", "Jones", "and", "Stanley", "is", "located", "in", "Shawnstad."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Kevin", "Green", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2686863", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Lisa", "Dixon", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-9419134", "and", "diagnosed", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Robert", "Ortiz,", "MRN", "MRN-2681042.", "Diagnosis:", "COPD.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Randy", "Wright", "(MRN:", "MRN-1087161,", "DOB:", "08/19/1971).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Rebecca", "Walker", "at", "gary79@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Hill", "PLC", "is", "located", "in", "Dunnville."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Jennifer", "Christensen", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8115687", "and", "diagnosed", "COPD.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Michael", "Hansen", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-5072543", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Charles", "Clark", "at", "amanda98@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Trujillo", "PLC", "is", "located", "in", "Tiffanyport."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Anthony", "Hoffman", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Tran-Jones.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "823-46-8438.", "Phone:", "(272)", "903-4824."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jack", "Galloway", "(SSN:", "266-57-6820),", "who", "works", "at", "Allen-Allen", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(414)", "886-5374", "or", "millertodd@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Kenneth", "Long", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8815384", "and", "diagnosed", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Prescribed", "Amoxicillin", "250mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Mark", "Jimenez", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Gardner,", "May", "and", "Turner.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "489-67-8253.", "Phone:", "(504)", "802-8025."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Sara", "Carpenter", "from", "Burns,", "Hernandez", "and", "Ryan", "was", "held", "in", "Mollybury.", "Contact:", "(591)", "239-8711,", "email", "martin86@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Donna", "Stuart,", "MRN", "MRN-5949685.", "Diagnosis:", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Scott", "Wilson", "at", "Long,", "Anderson", "and", "Irwin", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "693-94-9022", "and", "callback", "to", "(352)", "657-9824."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Tracy", "Carter", "at", "nicholas65@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Chen,", "Faulkner", "and", "Casey", "is", "located", "in", "New", "Wendy."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Grace", "Reeves", "at", "Nichols,", "Glover", "and", "Knox", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "794-83-8218", "and", "callback", "to", "(672)", "987-5616."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Luis", "Rice", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-6080688", "and", "diagnosed", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Melanie", "Mosley,", "MRN", "MRN-3760475,", "DOB", "01/24/1998,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Taylor", "York", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-9692311", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Susan", "Olson", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2140312", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Ms.", "Jennifer", "Hill", "at", "Fry,", "Hobbs", "and", "Buck", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "425-70-7246", "and", "callback", "to", "(595)", "879-3492."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Frank", "Hernandez", "DVM,", "MRN", "MRN-1158547.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Richard", "Jimenez,", "MRN", "MRN-1781180,", "DOB", "04/01/1962,", "presents", "with", "Hypertension.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Christina", "Gross", "(MRN:", "MRN-3193891,", "DOB:", "11/17/1980).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Scott", "Taylor", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Cooper", "PLC.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "971-25-5670.", "Phone:", "(285)", "981-3626."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Joseph", "Chang,", "MRN", "MRN-9106820,", "DOB", "02/01/1945,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Steven", "Wright", "(MRN:", "MRN-3725462,", "DOB:", "12/28/1962).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Denise", "Wong", "(MRN:", "MRN-8700704,", "DOB:", "12/20/1973).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Sherry", "Luna", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-5063384", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Aaron", "Vincent", "DVM,", "MRN", "MRN-2346371,", "DOB", "01/15/1997,", "presents", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Robert", "Torres", "at", "eddie35@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Terry,", "Williams", "and", "Huff", "is", "located", "in", "Lake", "Kentburgh."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Jesus", "Obrien", "from", "Taylor,", "Velazquez", "and", "Flores", "was", "held", "in", "Williamhaven.", "Contact:", "(345)", "273-1977,", "email", "vewing@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Richard", "Gibson", "(SSN:", "241-75-9085),", "who", "works", "at", "Horton-Cross", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(293)", "973-1771", "or", "smoore@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Angela", "Hernandez", "from", "Benson-Mccarthy", "was", "held", "in", "Brownchester.", "Contact:", "(311)", "454-4139,", "email", "perrymark@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Keith", "Stephens", "MD", "(MRN:", "MRN-3329349,", "DOB:", "04/30/1969).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Justin", "Riley", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Glass,", "Cunningham", "and", "Reid.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "316-68-6355.", "Phone:", "(545)", "979-7211."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Paul", "Larsen", "(SSN:", "462-64-7735),", "who", "works", "at", "Cannon-Boyd", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(678)", "946-1887", "or", "joshuajones@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Madison", "Marshall", "at", "torrestravis@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Turner,", "Ortiz", "and", "Taylor", "is", "located", "in", "New", "Derek."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Sandra", "Walker", "(MRN:", "MRN-9832465,", "DOB:", "12/01/1940).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Warfarin", "5mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Laurie", "Li", "(SSN:", "606-61-4997),", "who", "works", "at", "Murphy", "and", "Sons", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(351)", "871-1090", "or", "ramireztracey@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Andrew", "Gonzales", "(SSN:", "814-40-7274),", "who", "works", "at", "Robinson,", "Shields", "and", "Brown", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(439)", "994-7730", "or", "jim95@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Janet", "Williams", "from", "Walker-Velasquez", "was", "held", "in", "North", "Donna.", "Contact:", "(270)", "978-9727,", "email", "ybailey@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "James", "Ramsey,", "MRN", "MRN-5896386,", "DOB", "06/09/1953,", "presents", "with", "COPD.", "Current", "medication:", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Leslie", "Bell", "at", "brownmarie@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Collins", "Group", "is", "located", "in", "New", "Brookefurt."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Angela", "Ramirez,", "MRN", "MRN-6244264.", "Diagnosis:", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Amy", "Silva", "at", "Calhoun,", "Schmidt", "and", "Brown", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "256-90-3621", "and", "callback", "to", "(896)", "632-2040."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Lauren", "Vazquez,", "MRN", "MRN-6312979,", "DOB", "05/22/1985,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "David", "Davenport", "(SSN:", "490-83-6881),", "who", "works", "at", "Rhodes-Fernandez", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(788)", "502-5837", "or", "icampos@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Anna", "Lozano", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Wilkerson-Arias.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "824-29-8135.", "Phone:", "(380)", "951-9548."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Ruben", "Huff", "(MRN:", "MRN-4019585,", "DOB:", "02/15/1961).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Austin", "Santiago", "(SSN:", "238-19-8406),", "who", "works", "at", "Hancock", "Group", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(376)", "930-8292", "or", "harrismaria@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Kimberly", "Mitchell", "at", "Li,", "Craig", "and", "Drake", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "279-20-7267", "and", "callback", "to", "(834)", "899-4945."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Luke", "Miller", "(MRN:", "MRN-5952504,", "DOB:", "02/21/2003).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Heather", "Jones", "from", "Quinn", "Ltd", "was", "held", "in", "North", "Michael.", "Contact:", "(769)", "210-9464,", "email", "ingramjill@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Amber", "Campbell", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Khan,", "Pena", "and", "Ruiz.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "805-86-8699.", "Phone:", "(498)", "233-4792."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Kellie", "Marsh,", "MRN", "MRN-7658817.", "Diagnosis:", "Hypertension.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Christina", "Herrera", "at", "Murphy", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "833-47-9337", "and", "callback", "to", "(922)", "479-7807."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Kelly", "Haynes", "at", "wagnerdana@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Ellis-Adkins", "is", "located", "in", "New", "Ashleychester."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Danielle", "Wheeler", "(SSN:", "490-86-8668),", "who", "works", "at", "Miller,", "Sandoval", "and", "Cunningham", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(741)", "457-1188", "or", "sarah35@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Jonathan", "Hansen", "(MRN:", "MRN-9022561,", "DOB:", "11/13/1971).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Julie", "Fowler", "(MRN:", "MRN-8744735,", "DOB:", "06/26/1961).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Darryl", "Davis", "(SSN:", "643-47-8433),", "who", "works", "at", "Garcia", "LLC", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(717)", "819-8048", "or", "derrick22@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Juan", "Jordan", "(SSN:", "897-77-1009),", "who", "works", "at", "Parker", "Inc", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(813)", "531-9005", "or", "jason31@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Mr.", "Jason", "Thomas,", "MRN", "MRN-3540594.", "Diagnosis:", "COPD.", "Adjusting", "Sertraline", "50mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Isaac", "Patterson", "at", "bgonzalez@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Colon-Weber", "is", "located", "in", "Lake", "Kelly."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "April", "Woods", "at", "ssmith@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Wheeler", "PLC", "is", "located", "in", "Port", "Robertberg."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Hannah", "Ochoa", "(MRN:", "MRN-9430894,", "DOB:", "08/28/1951).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Jasmine", "Frye", "from", "Edwards,", "Arnold", "and", "Smith", "was", "held", "in", "Kariside.", "Contact:", "(235)", "329-2101,", "email", "james73@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jacob", "Ramos", "at", "Foley", "Inc", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "330-35-3414", "and", "callback", "to", "(225)", "247-5011."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Shelley", "Quinn", "from", "Wise", "Inc", "was", "held", "in", "Jennifershire.", "Contact:", "(791)", "719-4485,", "email", "lindsay48@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Amber", "Kim", "at", "wmacias@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Costa-Wilkerson", "is", "located", "in", "Garciafort."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Andrea", "Young", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Washington,", "Ryan", "and", "Cummings.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "963-17-4752.", "Phone:", "(232)", "523-7572."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Robert", "Reed,", "MRN", "MRN-9541658,", "DOB", "12/31/1992,", "presents", "with", "COPD.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Kyle", "Johnson", "at", "katie32@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Brown-Frey", "is", "located", "in", "Lake", "John."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Peter", "Perez", "at", "rsheppard@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Randall", "PLC", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Kent."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Hayley", "Ballard,", "MRN", "MRN-5872986,", "DOB", "05/30/2001,", "presents", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Melissa", "Hernandez", "(MRN:", "MRN-7989166,", "DOB:", "07/08/1976).", "Admitted", "for", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Claire", "Obrien,", "MRN", "MRN-1317716.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Dan", "Dougherty", "at", "Duran", "LLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "651-79-4613", "and", "callback", "to", "(699)", "424-5471."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Sharon", "Coffey", "from", "Smith,", "Buck", "and", "Holland", "was", "held", "in", "Rodneyfurt.", "Contact:", "(811)", "585-3527,", "email", "walkercharlene@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Carlos", "Smith", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-9816043", "and", "diagnosed", "COPD.", "Prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Misty", "Arias", "(MRN:", "MRN-5316188,", "DOB:", "05/20/1964).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Metformin", "500mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Rachel", "Leon", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Simpson", "Inc.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "847-22-6120.", "Phone:", "(637)", "520-5176."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Michael", "Paul", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Barnes,", "Newton", "and", "Moore.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "779-91-6491.", "Phone:", "(295)", "969-4848."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Daniel", "King", "(MRN:", "MRN-8944327,", "DOB:", "05/19/1996).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Rebecca", "Gutierrez,", "MRN", "MRN-1933413.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Amoxicillin", "250mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Nancy", "Stewart", "(SSN:", "751-34-5106),", "who", "works", "at", "Davis", "LLC", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(894)", "973-3240", "or", "rward@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Cody", "Williams", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Wilson-Jones.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "350-57-5669.", "Phone:", "(361)", "648-9900."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Tiffany", "Myers", "from", "Johnson,", "Guzman", "and", "Mccall", "was", "held", "in", "West", "Julie.", "Contact:", "(559)", "944-3419,", "email", "daniellegarcia@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Lisa", "Diaz,", "MRN", "MRN-5137094.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Sertraline", "50mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jacob", "Preston", "at", "Gonzales,", "Huber", "and", "Morgan", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "514-98-4986", "and", "callback", "to", "(513)", "879-7046."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Patrick", "Lane,", "MRN", "MRN-9460003,", "DOB", "10/04/1976,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jesse", "Rogers", "at", "Ramirez-Bean", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "597-71-4502", "and", "callback", "to", "(610)", "260-3697."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Erica", "Ramos", "from", "Lewis,", "Kennedy", "and", "Santana", "was", "held", "in", "Clarencebury.", "Contact:", "(924)", "846-1964,", "email", "donnacampbell@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Melinda", "Serrano", "(MRN:", "MRN-8711874,", "DOB:", "05/04/1979).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Warfarin", "5mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jay", "Mcneil", "at", "Harris-Carson", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "636-76-3600", "and", "callback", "to", "(572)", "581-5634."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Jenny", "Ayers", "(MRN:", "MRN-8728009,", "DOB:", "07/07/1937).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Rebecca", "Wright,", "MRN", "MRN-2373555,", "DOB", "06/17/1967,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Cynthia", "Martin", "at", "jillcook@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Keith", "Inc", "is", "located", "in", "West", "Erik."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Gina", "Booker,", "MRN", "MRN-5525929,", "DOB", "08/02/1990,", "presents", "with", "Hypertension.", "Current", "medication:", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["David", "Brown", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Chapman", "and", "Sons.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "573-58-5422.", "Phone:", "(855)", "904-4598."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Debra", "Daniels", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Weaver-Sherman.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "321-39-6383.", "Phone:", "(992)", "351-1046."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Jeffrey", "Roberson", "at", "unovak@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Jacobs-Austin", "is", "located", "in", "Kristenmouth."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Jordan", "Moore", "from", "Walker-Rodriguez", "was", "held", "in", "Bruceside.", "Contact:", "(753)", "282-3267,", "email", "danny49@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Debra", "Obrien", "from", "Barnes", "Inc", "was", "held", "in", "New", "James.", "Contact:", "(633)", "313-5720,", "email", "campbellkristen@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Danielle", "Vang", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-1900876", "and", "diagnosed", "Hypertension.", "Prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Diane", "Martinez,", "MRN", "MRN-8279795,", "DOB", "02/21/1967,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Matthew", "Velez", "(SSN:", "137-68-2442),", "who", "works", "at", "Pearson", "and", "Sons", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(522)", "458-6296", "or", "gentrygregory@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "David", "Douglas", "Jr.", "from", "Osborne", "and", "Sons", "was", "held", "in", "New", "Johnville.", "Contact:", "(752)", "335-8744,", "email", "lindadominguez@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Christopher", "Knight,", "MRN", "MRN-4609524,", "DOB", "06/10/1976,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Michael", "Holmes", "(MRN:", "MRN-5437118,", "DOB:", "11/29/1992).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Brandon", "Smith", "(MRN:", "MRN-4854842,", "DOB:", "12/28/1950).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Prednisone", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Alex", "Wagner", "at", "Richardson", "Ltd", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "949-70-3273", "and", "callback", "to", "(977)", "922-8685."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Shawn", "Collins", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Reyes", "PLC.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "341-59-2337.", "Phone:", "(583)", "429-1461."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Kayla", "Rodriguez", "at", "Walker,", "Gilbert", "and", "Acosta", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "151-81-5082", "and", "callback", "to", "(324)", "667-3184."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "John", "Sanchez", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2882551", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Paul", "Diaz", "(MRN:", "MRN-9453969,", "DOB:", "05/19/1964).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Julie", "Johnson", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Mann-Warner.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "388-87-4450.", "Phone:", "(934)", "551-4335."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Christina", "Morton", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Murphy,", "Willis", "and", "Hines.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "675-81-6400.", "Phone:", "(886)", "325-7730."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Brendan", "Zuniga", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-6249960", "and", "diagnosed", "COPD.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Cynthia", "Hamilton", "(MRN:", "MRN-5134741,", "DOB:", "03/27/1936).", "Admitted", "for", "Hypertension,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Kimberly", "Garza,", "MRN", "MRN-9790328,", "DOB", "06/18/1968,", "presents", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Current", "medication:", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Derek", "Long", "(MRN:", "MRN-3419132,", "DOB:", "10/16/1974).", "Admitted", "for", "COPD,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Sherri", "Davis", "at", "brettgarrett@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Wright-Watson", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Diana."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Daniel", "Figueroa,", "MRN", "MRN-3164813,", "DOB", "02/17/1988,", "presents", "with", "COPD.", "Current", "medication:", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Kimberly", "Newman", "MD", "(MRN:", "MRN-4293399,", "DOB:", "03/03/1984).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Daniel", "Hunt", "at", "Jordan-Campbell", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "489-71-1096", "and", "callback", "to", "(560)", "505-7389."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
