{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "284842079", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Deborah", "Herrera", "at", "Diaz,", "Hill", "and", "Becker."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "April", "Woods", "at", "Wheeler", "PLC", "has", "social", "security", "number", "084483679", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Andrea", "Young", "to", "049152505.", "Current", "employer:", "Washington,", "Ryan", "and", "Cummings."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Brazilian", "patient", "Tiffany", "Howard,", "MRN", "MRN-8250013,", "DOB", "03/05/1984,", "presented", "with", "COPD.", "Started", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Alicia", "Smith", "(MRN:", "MRN-2600296,", "DOB:", "09/21/1988).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Richard", "Joseph", "(German", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-4306357.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis,", "prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Shannon", "Stone", "at", "Buchanan", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "518-59-3945", "and", "callback", "to", "(515)", "709-1379."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Scott", "Johnson", "to", "394796851.", "Current", "employer:", "Lester,", "Mcbride", "and", "Byrd."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Joshua", "Howard", "(Korean", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-1262699.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "prescribed", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Spanish", "employee", "Richard", "Gibson", "at", "Horton-Cross", "has", "SSN", "624-26-2505", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(719)", "308-5889."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "332914795", "for", "Susan", "Miller", "at", "Mcdowell,", "Ortiz", "and", "Lopez", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Nathaniel", "Conway,", "MRN", "MRN-8052503.", "Diagnosis:", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Adjusting", "Albuterol", "inhaler", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Vincent", "Rivera", "to", "256167479.", "Current", "employer:", "Sawyer", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Douglas", "Baker,", "MRN", "MRN-3588336,", "DOB", "12/02/1946,", "presents", "with", "COPD.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "625842689", "registered", "to", "Paul", "Diaz", "at", "Ramirez-White."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "890941527", "registered", "to", "Linda", "Bautista", "at", "Bowman", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Justin", "Barnett", "to", "549983034.", "Current", "employer:", "Jones-Hensley."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Victor", "Gibson", "at", "phone", "number", "048137530", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Andrews-Green."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "034363684", "for", "Ruth", "Guerrero", "at", "Shepherd-Cortez", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jared", "Chavez", "(SSN:", "371-50-9294),", "who", "works", "at", "Pierce,", "Davis", "and", "Garcia", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(329)", "268-4866", "or", "davidbrown@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Cynthia", "Butler", "at", "Barnett,", "Mills", "and", "Ward", "has", "social", "security", "number", "792528432", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Melissa", "Williams,", "MRN", "MRN-3347981,", "DOB", "01/10/1963,", "presents", "with", "Hypertension.", "Current", "medication:", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Rhonda", "Benjamin", "(MRN:", "MRN-2049645,", "DOB:", "06/25/1947).", "Admitted", "for", "Hypertension,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "881552166", "registered", "to", "Sarah", "Watson", "at", "Vasquez-Galloway."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tiffany", "Myers", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Johnson,", "Guzman", "and", "Mccall.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "057-16-8489.", "Phone:", "(986)", "332-8088."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Jessica", "Smith,", "a", "Mexican", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Walker-Burgess", "in", "West", "Whitney.", "Contact:", "(577)", "493-2257", "or", "seanmyers@example.net."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Misty", "Walker", "(MRN:", "MRN-6347476,", "DOB:", "12/10/2004).", "Admitted", "for", "COPD,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Rebecca", "Walker", "to", "372402954.", "Current", "employer:", "Hill", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Anna", "Lozano", "at", "gbrown@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Wilkerson-Arias", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Virginia."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Matthew", "Espinoza,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "453814962,", "employed", "at", "Jones-Ewing."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Pamela", "Thompson,", "a", "Chinese", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Pearson,", "Moon", "and", "White", "in", "Baileymouth.", "Contact:", "(882)", "618-6344", "or", "fwalters@example.org."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Charles", "Mendez", "at", "Sanchez,", "Phillips", "and", "Jenkins", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "269-34-7312", "and", "callback", "to", "(711)", "730-7340."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Angela", "Hernandez,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "674759261,", "employed", "at", "Benson-Mccarthy."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Jeff", "Owens", "at", "Brown,", "Valdez", "and", "Lucas", "has", "social", "security", "number", "480684120", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Christine", "Soto", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-6354241", "and", "diagnosed", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Prescribed", "Prednisone", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Benjamin", "Thompson,", "MRN", "MRN-8356053.", "Diagnosis:", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Patricia", "Collins,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "800075439,", "employed", "at", "Tran", "Inc."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "John", "Figueroa,", "MRN", "MRN-4786141.", "Diagnosis:", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Adjusting", "Metformin", "500mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Riley", "Bryant", "(SSN:", "411-98-9013),", "who", "works", "at", "Copeland", "Group", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(537)", "621-9117", "or", "chenbailey@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Donald", "Jones", "from", "Bell-Hicks", "was", "held", "in", "Benjaminchester.", "Contact:", "(299)", "874-8062,", "email", "sheila14@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Chinese", "taxpayer", "Nancy", "Stewart", "at", "Davis", "LLC", "has", "SSN", "080419434", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Joy", "Meyer", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-1191859", "and", "diagnosed", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Tracy", "Carter", "to", "617201235.", "Current", "employer:", "Chen,", "Faulkner", "and", "Casey."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jennifer", "Lynch", "(Indian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-7901115.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Stephen", "Watson", "(MRN:", "MRN-9010256,", "DOB:", "12/01/1977).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jason", "Marshall", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Lawson-Edwards.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "580-88-2951.", "Phone:", "(583)", "641-3385."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Kimberly", "Rich", "(MRN:", "MRN-2387242,", "DOB:", "01/02/1966).", "Admitted", "for", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "James", "Griffin", "at", "Finley-Turner", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "869-59-1502", "and", "callback", "to", "(262)", "607-5520."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Paul", "Brennan", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Mcdowell-Smith.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "714-70-6867.", "Phone:", "(597)", "664-7078."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Brian", "Martin", "at", "jcervantes@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Steele-Roberts", "is", "located", "in", "Millerview."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Brianna", "Brown", "(MRN:", "MRN-5703878,", "DOB:", "06/06/1992).", "Admitted", "for", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "William", "Jackson", "at", "sean43@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Underwood", "Ltd", "is", "located", "in", "West", "Jonathanville."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Donald", "Evans", "to", "348295457.", "Current", "employer:", "Ward", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Sharon", "Beard,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "612847711,", "employed", "at", "Baker-Pena."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Brent", "Hopkins", "(MRN:", "MRN-8876742,", "DOB:", "05/01/1935).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "793972182", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Kevin", "Nguyen", "at", "Hensley,", "Lopez", "and", "Baker."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Italian", "taxpayer", "Cynthia", "Snyder", "at", "Spencer-Wood", "has", "SSN", "103571634", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Michael", "Bradley", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-2834801", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Russian", "employee", "Jesus", "Obrien", "at", "Taylor,", "Velazquez", "and", "Flores", "has", "SSN", "509-37-3771", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(779)", "902-1803."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tom", "Williams", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Hamilton,", "Ramsey", "and", "Crawford.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "256-15-0425.", "Phone:", "(742)", "575-7521."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Pamela", "Romero", "(SSN:", "571-29-5314),", "who", "works", "at", "Harrell", "LLC", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(673)", "588-5422", "or", "ericfarmer@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Italian", "patient", "Angel", "Zimmerman,", "MRN", "MRN-2503554,", "DOB", "07/11/1973,", "presented", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Started", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Dan", "Dougherty", "at", "Duran", "LLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "278-40-4119", "and", "callback", "to", "(635)", "963-6419."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Barry", "Bernard", "from", "Webster", "and", "Sons", "was", "held", "in", "South", "Elizabeth.", "Contact:", "(883)", "767-5905,", "email", "maryhowell@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "331375534", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Kelly", "Mclaughlin", "at", "Calhoun", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "employee", "Ryan", "Parker", "at", "Ruiz-Jacobson", "has", "SSN", "496-60-3343", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(274)", "905-1981."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Mexican", "patient", "Holly", "Chapman,", "MRN", "MRN-7298619,", "DOB", "01/29/1989,", "presented", "with", "COPD.", "Started", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Cynthia", "Martin", "to", "498288835.", "Current", "employer:", "Keith", "Inc."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "170792282", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Larry", "Carey", "at", "Banks,", "Boyd", "and", "Wood."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Paul", "Martin", "DVM", "(MRN:", "MRN-7801762,", "DOB:", "06/13/1994).", "Admitted", "for", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Michael", "King", "(Mexican", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-7795568.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "prescribed", "Amoxicillin", "250mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Kari", "Lee", "from", "Maynard-Wagner", "was", "held", "in", "Burnsland.", "Contact:", "(858)", "536-3093,", "email", "fortiz@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Gabrielle", "Davis", "to", "604360107.", "Current", "employer:", "Howard", "LLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Laura", "Williams", "at", "Graves-Weaver", "has", "social", "security", "number", "432681863", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Mr.", "Matthew", "Steele", "(Korean", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-4603680.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Australian", "taxpayer", "Jeremy", "Jones", "at", "Moreno", "Group", "has", "SSN", "566988904", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Carmen", "Rose", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Henderson,", "Lewis", "and", "Ryan.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "470-19-4340.", "Phone:", "(871)", "711-7482."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Anthony", "Anderson,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "809319648,", "employed", "at", "Bryant-Brown."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Australian", "employee", "Gregory", "Hill", "at", "Cannon,", "Johnson", "and", "Keller", "has", "SSN", "455-10-1324", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(636)", "902-2768."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Sabrina", "Briggs", "at", "Garcia", "LLC", "has", "social", "security", "number", "130828043", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Japanese", "patient", "Ruth", "Richard,", "MRN", "MRN-7027375,", "DOB", "05/28/1959,", "presented", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Started", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Kelly", "Haynes,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "106115373,", "employed", "at", "Ellis-Adkins."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "French", "employee", "Jennifer", "Mitchell", "at", "Mason,", "Perry", "and", "Miles", "has", "SSN", "192-86-1403", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(639)", "201-6780."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Patrick", "Harris", "(MRN:", "MRN-7655572,", "DOB:", "08/07/1998).", "Admitted", "for", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "treated", "with", "Metformin", "500mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Japanese", "citizen", "Kristie", "Willis", "at", "Hoffman,", "Santiago", "and", "Jenkins.", "SSN:", "851-12-4570,", "callback", "(646)", "948-5397."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "April", "Fitzgerald", "(Canadian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-1813936.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Italian", "citizen", "Jordan", "Moore", "at", "Walker-Rodriguez.", "SSN:", "389-44-0471,", "callback", "(449)", "968-8613."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "422797249", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Selena", "Gonzalez", "at", "Hernandez,", "Shaffer", "and", "Thompson."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Brian", "James", "(French", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-2599906.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Todd", "Jacobson", "at", "david49@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "King", "Ltd", "is", "located", "in", "New", "Danielleshire."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Travis", "Joyce,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "706396595,", "employed", "at", "Hammond-Strickland."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Terri", "Mckinney", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-8986040", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Christine", "Whitehead,", "MRN", "MRN-2637842,", "DOB", "04/30/1997,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Benjamin", "Mcmahon,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "657999450,", "employed", "at", "Morgan", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Alexandra", "Taylor,", "MRN", "MRN-8115687.", "Diagnosis:", "COPD.", "Adjusting", "Sertraline", "50mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Thomas", "Weaver", "DDS,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "720985063,", "employed", "at", "Warren", "Inc."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Debra", "Daniels,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "141201265,", "employed", "at", "Weaver-Sherman."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Jeffrey", "Smith", "(SSN:", "347-87-9796),", "who", "works", "at", "Harris", "Ltd", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(572)", "581-5634", "or", "raylauren@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lance", "Short", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Carter,", "Garcia", "and", "Murphy.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "484-32-7484.", "Phone:", "(721)", "922-5479."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "David", "Griffith", "at", "Wilson-Herrera", "has", "social", "security", "number", "719146268", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Ann", "Phillips", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Perry,", "Gonzalez", "and", "Buchanan.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "399-44-6625.", "Phone:", "(699)", "424-5471."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Japanese", "patient", "Jessica", "Perez,", "MRN", "MRN-8558977,", "DOB", "06/09/1981,", "presented", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Started", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Jamie", "Baird,", "a", "German", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Blevins-Ballard", "in", "Julieborough.", "Contact:", "(292)", "604-1228", "or", "bobby15@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Tiffany", "Curtis", "(MRN:", "MRN-4477544,", "DOB:", "12/02/1948).", "Admitted", "for", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis,", "treated", "with", "Warfarin", "5mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Mark", "Roberts", "at", "xcollier@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Smith-Nguyen", "is", "located", "in", "Richardbury."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Korean", "citizen", "Shannon", "Malone", "at", "Sullivan", "Group.", "SSN:", "691-11-4459,", "callback", "(253)", "359-3579."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Jeremy", "Mcintyre", "(MRN:", "MRN-2993318,", "DOB:", "11/22/1964).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Valerie", "Howard", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7642917", "and", "diagnosed", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Prescribed", "Metformin", "500mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Hayden", "Shannon", "at", "phone", "number", "440841495", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "White-Reese."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Sarah", "Phillips,", "MRN", "MRN-9703982.", "Diagnosis:", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Adjusting", "Prednisone", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Thomas", "Webb", "(MRN:", "MRN-4645172,", "DOB:", "09/14/1976).", "Admitted", "for", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Mexican", "patient", "Jaime", "Bowman,", "MRN", "MRN-8899184,", "DOB", "06/22/1991,", "presented", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Started", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Jeffrey", "Roberson", "to", "510967056.", "Current", "employer:", "Jacobs-Austin."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Mr.", "Gerald", "Rowe", "at", "phone", "number", "310214490", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Murray,", "Matthews", "and", "Johnson."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "321163909", "for", "Robin", "Riley", "at", "Lewis,", "Johnson", "and", "Green", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Gina", "Wilson", "from", "Taylor", "and", "Sons", "was", "held", "in", "Christopherfurt.", "Contact:", "(678)", "330-9751,", "email", "zcoffey@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "French", "employee", "Nicole", "Thompson", "at", "Prince,", "Wilcox", "and", "Robertson", "has", "SSN", "102-88-6019", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(422)", "654-8285."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Joseph", "Santos", "at", "Morton,", "Medina", "and", "Webb", "has", "social", "security", "number", "078892443", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Andrew", "Gonzales", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Perez-Adams.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "752-45-6533.", "Phone:", "(821)", "347-6121."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Japanese", "patient", "Nathaniel", "Johnson,", "MRN", "MRN-6111313,", "DOB", "11/25/1972,", "presented", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Started", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Michelle", "Evans", "at", "Richardson", "Ltd", "has", "social", "security", "number", "774932241", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "British", "citizen", "Kimberly", "Mitchell", "at", "Li,", "Craig", "and", "Drake.", "SSN:", "221-49-6879,", "callback", "(958)", "848-1502."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Diana", "Daniels", "at", "brendagoodwin@example.net.", "Their", "office", "at", "Johnson,", "Mcfarland", "and", "Edwards", "is", "located", "in", "Hickmanport."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Roberto", "Bartlett", "(MRN:", "MRN-9376917,", "DOB:", "12/05/1964).", "Admitted", "for", "Acute", "Bronchitis,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "413664559", "for", "Brandon", "Thomas", "at", "Graham,", "Brown", "and", "Walker", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Korean", "patient", "Alexandria", "Oneill,", "MRN", "MRN-1786584,", "DOB", "06/25/1973,", "presented", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Started", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "173599268", "registered", "to", "Mr.", "Daniel", "Martin", "at", "Johnson-Williams."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "440412291", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Mark", "Cole", "at", "Green-Ward."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Allison", "Smith", "at", "Chapman", "Inc", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "204-10-9701", "and", "callback", "to", "(519)", "789-7149."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Tina", "Smith,", "MRN", "MRN-2754047,", "DOB", "01/11/1999,", "presents", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Current", "medication:", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Jerry", "Christensen,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "316470654,", "employed", "at", "Bishop,", "Gray", "and", "Johnson."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Clinton", "Jensen", "(MRN:", "MRN-6037595,", "DOB:", "08/15/1953).", "Admitted", "for", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "treated", "with", "Lisinopril", "10mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Julian", "Conner", "at", "Cole", "PLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "122-72-6819", "and", "callback", "to", "(352)", "776-5978."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Kayla", "Rodriguez", "(SSN:", "825-16-9273),", "who", "works", "at", "Walker,", "Gilbert", "and", "Acosta", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(304)", "913-5941", "or", "stephen00@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Mark", "Jimenez,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "333084807,", "employed", "at", "Gardner,", "May", "and", "Turner."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "377392247", "registered", "to", "Joyce", "Martinez", "at", "Stevens,", "Norris", "and", "Smith."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Jessica", "Wilson,", "MRN", "MRN-4736121.", "Diagnosis:", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Adjusting", "Metformin", "500mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Christina", "Herrera", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Murphy", "PLC.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "134-70-4107.", "Phone:", "(810)", "202-5542."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "803318109", "registered", "to", "Evan", "Carter", "at", "Jacobs-Foster."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Erin", "Carter", "(MRN:", "MRN-3845129,", "DOB:", "07/18/2004).", "Admitted", "for", "COPD,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jonathan", "Martinez", "(Chinese", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-3570027.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis,", "prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Melanie", "Wells", "(MRN:", "MRN-2843740,", "DOB:", "10/30/1944).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Metformin", "500mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Charles", "Hill", "at", "Wright", "PLC", "has", "social", "security", "number", "296314935", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Kelly", "Hartman,", "MRN", "MRN-6443037.", "Diagnosis:", "COPD.", "Adjusting", "Metformin", "500mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Cody", "Williams,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "886094574,", "employed", "at", "Wilson-Jones."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Shelly", "Spencer,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "041565281,", "employed", "at", "Dawson", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Mark", "Copeland", "to", "165357362.", "Current", "employer:", "Martinez", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Leslie", "Bell", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Collins", "Group.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "591-81-0879.", "Phone:", "(689)", "316-2070."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Jason", "Butler", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Anderson,", "Sanchez", "and", "Harris.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "682-33-6133.", "Phone:", "(608)", "625-2557."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Wesley", "Ayala,", "MRN", "MRN-4369728.", "Diagnosis:", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "German", "employee", "Michael", "Poole", "at", "Long,", "Thomas", "and", "Chen", "has", "SSN", "804-61-3179", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(439)", "746-4918."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Dr.", "Samuel", "Holmes", "DDS", "at", "phone", "number", "089132294", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Evans-Hart."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "Mexican", "citizen", "Rachel", "Leon", "at", "Simpson", "Inc.", "SSN:", "469-09-1817,", "callback", "(248)", "444-7878."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Shawn", "Collins", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-5161539", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Hector", "Norton", "from", "Watson", "Group", "was", "held", "in", "Gabriellaland.", "Contact:", "(549)", "361-7062,", "email", "scunningham@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Spanish", "employee", "Joshua", "Gibson", "at", "Curry,", "Baker", "and", "James", "has", "SSN", "052-34-6212", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(858)", "638-3223."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "American", "taxpayer", "Mrs.", "Kristen", "Reyes", "at", "Romero,", "Suarez", "and", "Shields", "has", "SSN", "487791194", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "136763706", "registered", "to", "Dale", "Wright", "at", "Kelly,", "Maxwell", "and", "Wilson."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "patient", "Cindy", "Walker,", "MRN", "MRN-4817541,", "DOB", "08/09/1951,", "presented", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Started", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Gary", "Ramirez", "(Chinese", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-4195751.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes,", "prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Wendy", "Phillips,", "a", "Spanish", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Foster,", "Smith", "and", "Grimes", "in", "New", "Laurie.", "Contact:", "(625)", "263-4388", "or", "lozanojulie@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Stephen", "Sanford,", "MRN", "MRN-8768911.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Dr.", "Victoria", "Thomas", "(Australian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-2800206.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation,", "prescribed", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Mexican", "patient", "Christopher", "Sandoval,", "MRN", "MRN-5014486,", "DOB", "12/04/1975,", "presented", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Started", "Metformin", "500mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Latoya", "Miller,", "a", "Australian", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Moore", "PLC", "in", "Tuckermouth.", "Contact:", "(907)", "687-9041", "or", "craigjoseph@example.net."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "John", "Smith,", "MRN", "MRN-4240708.", "Diagnosis:", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Adjusting", "Albuterol", "inhaler", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Alfred", "Galvan,", "a", "Australian", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Santos,", "Moody", "and", "Taylor", "in", "Westtown.", "Contact:", "(790)", "241-3870", "or", "samantha72@example.net."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Justin", "Riley", "at", "michelle52@example.com.", "Their", "office", "at", "Glass,", "Cunningham", "and", "Reid", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Scottport."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "meeting", "between", "Kyle", "Johnson", "from", "Brown-Frey", "was", "held", "in", "Lake", "John.", "Contact:", "(930)", "655-2438,", "email", "katie32@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "497183197", "registered", "to", "Ashley", "Schmitt", "at", "Gallegos,", "Davenport", "and", "Baker."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "employee", "Bianca", "Carter", "at", "Howe-Long", "has", "SSN", "360-58-0694", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(513)", "656-7981."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Austin", "Schultz", "at", "phone", "number", "671474103", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Rhodes", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "440288106", "for", "Christopher", "Shea", "at", "Gomez-Foster", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Susan", "Arroyo", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-6541407", "and", "diagnosed", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Prescribed", "Lisinopril", "10mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Kelly", "Mccoy", "to", "874107407.", "Current", "employer:", "Norton,", "Mayo", "and", "Casey."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Brittany", "Serrano", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7923579", "and", "diagnosed", "COPD.", "Prescribed", "Amoxicillin", "250mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Lisa", "Kennedy", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-1625760", "and", "diagnosed", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Prescribed", "Albuterol", "inhaler.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Joseph", "Hanson,", "MRN", "MRN-9816043.", "Diagnosis:", "COPD.", "Adjusting", "Warfarin", "5mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "William", "Mcgee", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-6086650", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Mark", "Newman", "to", "782109404.", "Current", "employer:", "Willis,", "Lowery", "and", "Jones."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Italian", "patient", "Jennifer", "Bailey,", "MRN", "MRN-7506196,", "DOB", "08/29/1999,", "presented", "with", "Hypertension.", "Started", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Chinese", "taxpayer", "Heather", "Jones", "at", "Quinn", "Ltd", "has", "SSN", "531478168", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "360933491", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Kenneth", "Perez", "at", "Le", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "499828805", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Nicole", "Taylor", "at", "White", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Tammy", "Allison", "to", "740934316.", "Current", "employer:", "Russell", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Christopher", "Robinson", "(Indian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-2654343.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Danielle", "Wheeler", "(SSN:", "827-40-3924),", "who", "works", "at", "Miller,", "Sandoval", "and", "Cunningham", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(219)", "314-6947", "or", "sarah35@example.org."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Rebecca", "Mendez", "at", "phone", "number", "385581238", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Mann,", "Martin", "and", "Oconnell."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Joshua", "Ruiz", "to", "891305384.", "Current", "employer:", "Pham,", "Petersen", "and", "Gill."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Mr.", "Donald", "Nguyen", "(MRN:", "MRN-6007984,", "DOB:", "05/20/1955).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Atorvastatin", "20mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Jaclyn", "Moore", "to", "541786933.", "Current", "employer:", "Warner,", "Carr", "and", "Archer."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Juan", "Harding", "at", "Scott-Underwood", "has", "social", "security", "number", "232559191", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Priscilla", "Mcmillan", "at", "phone", "number", "116318186", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Matthews,", "Sheppard", "and", "Gutierrez."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "William", "Baker", "(MRN:", "MRN-7302286,", "DOB:", "10/29/1938).", "Admitted", "for", "Hypertension,", "treated", "with", "Amoxicillin", "250mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "James", "Miller", "to", "310028752.", "Current", "employer:", "Reese-Walker."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "British", "patient", "Jesus", "Houston,", "MRN", "MRN-5037710,", "DOB", "07/14/1985,", "presented", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Started", "Lisinopril", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Isaac", "Turner", "at", "Ferguson,", "Hill", "and", "Mccann", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "359-40-3729", "and", "callback", "to", "(681)", "427-4269."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "144245155", "registered", "to", "Crystal", "Baker", "at", "Williams", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Kathryn", "Snyder,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "869164921,", "employed", "at", "George", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Andrew", "Cruz", "at", "phone", "number", "466635363", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Mendez-Meyer."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Lisa", "Haynes,", "MRN", "MRN-9201172,", "DOB", "09/29/1965,", "presents", "with", "Hypertension.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jonathan", "Phillips,", "MRN", "MRN-5872986,", "DOB", "05/17/2001,", "presents", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Current", "medication:", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Nicholas", "Olson,", "MRN", "MRN-6045519,", "DOB", "08/16/1983,", "presents", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Ronald", "Herman", "at", "phone", "number", "580635632", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Bailey-Ochoa."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Kenneth", "Miller", "(MRN:", "MRN-4640933,", "DOB:", "07/23/1971).", "Admitted", "for", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis,", "treated", "with", "Sertraline", "50mg,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Peter", "Perez,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "248602008,", "employed", "at", "Randall", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Juan", "Jordan", "(SSN:", "061-30-1105),", "who", "works", "at", "Parker", "Inc", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(802)", "425-1117", "or", "jason31@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "589506932", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Jack", "Smith", "at", "Charles", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "employee", "Todd", "Hendrix", "at", "Bush-Vaughn", "has", "SSN", "232-87-6512", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(317)", "679-2233."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Leslie", "Powers,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "680195732,", "employed", "at", "Wilson-Torres."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "834270973", "for", "Joseph", "Perez", "at", "Clarke-James", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Chinese", "taxpayer", "Amanda", "Preston", "at", "Vaughn-Williams", "has", "SSN", "271945993", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Mexican", "patient", "Alexander", "Williams,", "MRN", "MRN-1447065,", "DOB", "07/02/1997,", "presented", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Started", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "406815006", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Michael", "Nicholson", "at", "Spencer", "and", "Sons."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Discharge", "summary", "for", "Sheryl", "Acosta", "(MRN:", "MRN-3403511,", "DOB:", "04/08/2000).", "Admitted", "for", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder,", "treated", "with", "Albuterol", "inhaler,", "stable", "at", "discharge."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Brazilian", "patient", "Alexandra", "Fisher,", "MRN", "MRN-8412854,", "DOB", "07/17/1942,", "presented", "with", "Hypertension.", "Started", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "David", "White", "at", "phone", "number", "275706011", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Greene-Elliott."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "American", "patient", "Melissa", "Thompson,", "MRN", "MRN-9484790,", "DOB", "09/07/1994,", "presented", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Started", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "David", "Davenport", "to", "210393461.", "Current", "employer:", "Rhodes-Fernandez."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Spanish", "patient", "David", "Miles,", "MRN", "MRN-3514105,", "DOB", "03/04/1950,", "presented", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Started", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Emily", "Hines", "to", "010604713.", "Current", "employer:", "Ferrell-Owens."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Maria", "Jones", "at", "Grant", "Group", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "102-98-3405", "and", "callback", "to", "(782)", "835-1986."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "American", "patient", "Ryan", "Garrison,", "MRN", "MRN-7139410,", "DOB", "03/01/1985,", "presented", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Started", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Sara", "Carpenter", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Burns,", "Hernandez", "and", "Ryan.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "507-52-3998.", "Phone:", "(624)", "844-4185."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Australian", "employee", "Randall", "Johnson", "at", "Murray,", "Erickson", "and", "Gonzales", "has", "SSN", "779-75-7355", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(991)", "843-9095."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Send", "the", "contract", "to", "Brian", "Harris", "at", "donna43@example.org.", "Their", "office", "at", "Ortiz", "PLC", "is", "located", "in", "South", "Ashleyfort."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 11, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 5, 6], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-EMAIL", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Tyler", "Vasquez", "at", "phone", "number", "010025630", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Duran", "PLC."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Timothy", "James,", "MRN", "MRN-7704473,", "DOB", "03/10/1995,", "presents", "with", "Atrial", "Fibrillation.", "Current", "medication:", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Haley", "Sparks", "at", "phone", "number", "501221355", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Smith,", "Macias", "and", "Gonzales."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Dr.", "Mark", "Marsh", "reviewed", "MRN", "MRN-7944595", "and", "diagnosed", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg.", "Follow-up", "in", "2", "weeks."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Michelle", "Hodges,", "MRN", "MRN-1531577.", "Diagnosis:", "Hypertension.", "Adjusting", "Albuterol", "inhaler", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Update", "the", "SSN", "for", "Jack", "Galloway", "to", "217735156.", "Current", "employer:", "Allen-Allen."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Veronica", "Brewer", "(SSN:", "463-65-3630),", "who", "works", "at", "Brooks-Vance", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(687)", "659-6931", "or", "ykane@example.com."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Kristin", "Haney,", "a", "Chinese", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Armstrong", "and", "Sons", "in", "Trevorland.", "Contact:", "(906)", "570-2443", "or", "rjackson@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Manuel", "Brock", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Alexander-Jordan.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "795-45-5753.", "Phone:", "(278)", "722-2868."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Bruce", "Brown", "(Indian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-1992583.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Hypertension,", "prescribed", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Australian", "patient", "Kayla", "Williamson,", "MRN", "MRN-8607331,", "DOB", "10/23/1955,", "presented", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Started", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Henry", "Pugh", "MD", "at", "Willis,", "James", "and", "Barton", "has", "social", "security", "number", "573865803", "on", "file."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Daniel", "Goodman", "at", "Jensen-Ramos", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "082-03-4194", "and", "callback", "to", "(977)", "922-8685."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "795313439", "for", "Dale", "Heath", "at", "Cohen,", "Serrano", "and", "Jacobs", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "patient", "Mark", "Powers,", "MRN", "MRN-3839807,", "DOB", "03/01/1944,", "presented", "with", "Acute", "Bronchitis.", "Started", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Lab", "results", "for", "patient", "Mr.", "Adam", "Davis,", "MRN", "MRN-2069713.", "Diagnosis:", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Adjusting", "Lisinopril", "10mg", "dosage."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Yolanda", "Parsons", "submitted", "an", "application", "to", "Mccullough,", "Hodges", "and", "Sanchez.", "SSN", "on", "file:", "451-50-5555.", "Phone:", "(327)", "576-8159."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "284831381", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Rhonda", "Cooper", "at", "Martinez-Dillon."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Michael", "Moreno", "(Canadian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-1609681.", "Diagnosed", "with", "COPD,", "prescribed", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "546369779", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Natalie", "Juarez", "at", "Johnston,", "Coleman", "and", "Scott."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Brazilian", "taxpayer", "Emily", "Collins", "at", "Hays-Daniels", "has", "SSN", "565029049", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "German", "patient", "Elizabeth", "Brown,", "MRN", "MRN-8494978,", "DOB", "07/05/1938,", "presented", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Started", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "taxpayer", "Charles", "Clark", "at", "Trujillo", "PLC", "has", "SSN", "710992713", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Background", "check", "for", "French", "citizen", "Jay", "Mcneil", "at", "Harris-Carson.", "SSN:", "511-66-7649,", "callback", "(363)", "535-6123."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 7, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Korean", "patient", "Jamie", "Montoya,", "MRN", "MRN-1663497,", "DOB", "12/03/1940,", "presented", "with", "Hypertension.", "Started", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Matthew", "Flores", "(Italian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-3283789.", "Diagnosed", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease,", "prescribed", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Mary", "Bryant", "(Indian", "national),", "MRN", "MRN-5748945.", "Diagnosed", "with", "COPD,", "prescribed", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 17, 0, 0, 13, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "896057369", "for", "Kevin", "Saunders", "at", "Keller,", "Baker", "and", "Ramsey", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Canadian", "patient", "Megan", "Hoffman,", "MRN", "MRN-7682298,", "DOB", "07/18/1951,", "presented", "with", "Hypertension.", "Started", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Serial", "number", "576658110", "registered", "to", "Carrie", "Valdez", "at", "Matthews-Villanueva."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Tax", "ID", "verification:", "Raven", "Mclaughlin,", "taxpayer", "identification", "number", "162922853,", "employed", "at", "Johnston", "Group."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 3, 4], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["Michael", "Farrell,", "a", "Chinese", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Rich,", "Arnold", "and", "Glenn", "in", "Mariafurt.", "Contact:", "(630)", "701-2729", "or", "ohayes@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Julie", "Johnson,", "a", "Chinese", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Mann-Warner", "in", "South", "Danny.", "Contact:", "(820)", "723-2894", "or", "ojones@example.com."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 6, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Tracking", "number", "779937232", "for", "the", "order", "placed", "by", "Nathan", "Stanley", "at", "Valentine-Robinson."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Mexican", "employee", "Chase", "Baker", "at", "Jones", "and", "Sons", "has", "SSN", "760-95-3229", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(201)", "732-9821."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Lisa", "Allen", "at", "Thomas,", "Murray", "and", "King", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "083-18-2472", "and", "callback", "to", "(440)", "478-6502."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "German", "taxpayer", "Jack", "White", "at", "Peterson", "Group", "has", "SSN", "296914633", "per", "tax", "records."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "British", "patient", "Linda", "Williams,", "MRN", "MRN-2373555,", "DOB", "01/23/1943,", "presented", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Started", "Warfarin", "5mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Italian", "patient", "Amber", "Wilson,", "MRN", "MRN-2882551,", "DOB", "08/10/1967,", "presented", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Started", "Sertraline", "50mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Karen", "Hoffman,", "MRN", "MRN-6052144,", "DOB", "01/28/1990,", "presents", "with", "Chronic", "Kidney", "Disease.", "Current", "medication:", "Prednisone", "10mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "French", "employee", "Alyssa", "Haynes", "at", "Elliott,", "Hart", "and", "Lopez", "has", "SSN", "243-64-0431", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(720)", "429-2988."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "567779831", "for", "Christina", "Johnston", "at", "Ryan,", "Krause", "and", "Mitchell", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Call", "Rebecca", "Hughes", "at", "phone", "number", "635075883", "regarding", "the", "shipment", "from", "Keith-Williams."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Russian", "patient", "Grace", "Reeves,", "MRN", "MRN-4590102,", "DOB", "04/09/1985,", "presented", "with", "Major", "Depressive", "Disorder.", "Started", "Atorvastatin", "20mg."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "British", "employee", "Lindsey", "Russo", "at", "Ballard", "PLC", "has", "SSN", "096-56-1583", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(903)", "685-2099."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["The", "Spanish", "employee", "Anthony", "Hoffman", "at", "Tran-Jones", "has", "SSN", "243-49-9371", "on", "file.", "Phone:", "(509)", "403-7302."], "ner_tags": [0, 17, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Jacqueline", "Cooper,", "MRN", "MRN-2893218,", "DOB", "06/25/1943,", "presents", "with", "Type", "2", "Diabetes.", "Current", "medication:", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Patient", "Sarah", "Turner,", "MRN", "MRN-8230636,", "DOB", "11/01/1992,", "presents", "with", "Rheumatoid", "Arthritis.", "Current", "medication:", "Albuterol", "inhaler."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 13, 0, 15, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MRN", "O", "B-DOB", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Angela", "Harrington,", "a", "Indian", "national,", "is", "employed", "by", "Morgan-Schwartz", "in", "Finleyfort.", "Contact:", "(675)", "883-9702", "or", "christianmelissa@example.net."], "ner_tags": [1, 2, 0, 17, 0, 0, 0, 0, 3, 0, 5, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Reference", "account", "number", "602155701", "for", "Jeremy", "Hampton", "at", "Arnold-Thompson", "on", "the", "invoice."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 0, 0, 0], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"tokens": ["Please", "summarize", "the", "case", "for", "Erica", "Ramos", "(SSN:", "061-22-6210),", "who", "works", "at", "Lewis,", "Kennedy", "and", "Santana", "and", "can", "be", "reached", "at", "(616)", "697-8886", "or", "donnacampbell@example.net."], "ner_tags": [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 3, 4, 4, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10, 0, 11], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE", "O", "B-EMAIL"]}
{"tokens": ["Employee", "Morgan", "Marsh", "at", "Freeman", "LLC", "reported", "a", "security", "incident.", "Verified", "identity", "via", "SSN", "577-13-1201", "and", "callback", "to", "(523)", "969-2188."], "ner_tags": [0, 1, 2, 0, 3, 4, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 7, 0, 0, 0, 9, 10], "ner_tag_labels": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SSN", "O", "O", "O", "B-PHONE", "I-PHONE"]}
